<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ArrayOfPlayerSpell xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You hurl a bubble of acid. Choose one creature within
range, or choose two creatures within range that are
within 5 feet of each other. A target must succeed on a
Dexterity saving throw or take 1d6 acid damage.
This spell’s damage increases by 1d6 when you reach
5th level (2d6), 11th level (3d6), and 17th level (4d6).</Description>
    <ItemName>Acid Splash</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Acid Splash</SpellName>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_NONE</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Your spell bolsters your allies with toughness and
resolve. Choose up to three creatures within range.
Each target’s hit point maximum and current hit points
increase by 5 for the duration.</Description>
    <ItemName>Aid</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Aid</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level or higher, a target’s hit points
increase by an additional 5 for each slot level above 2nd.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Abjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>2</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>4800</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a tiny strip of white cloth</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You set an alarm against unwanted intrusion. Choose
a door, a window, or an area within range that is no
larger than a 20-foot cube. Until the spell ends, an alarm
alerts you whenever a Tiny or larger creature touches
or enters the warded area. When you cast the spell, you
can designate creatures that won’t set off the alarm. You
also choose whether the alarm is mental or audible.
A mental alarm alerts you with a ping in your mind
if you are within 1 mile of the warded area. This ping
awakens you if you are sleeping. An audible alarm produces 
the sound of a hand bell for 10 seconds within 60 feet.</Description>
    <ItemName>Alarm</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Alarm</SpellName>
    <School>Abjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>4800</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_NONE</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>10</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You assume a different form. When you cast the spell,
choose one of the following options, the effects of which
last for the duration of the spell. 

While the spell lasts, you can end one option as an action to gain the benefits
of a different one.

Aquatic Adaptation. You adapt your body to an
aquatic environment, sprouting gills and growing
webbing between your fingers. You can breathe
underwater and gain a swimming speed equal to your
walking speed.

Change Appearance. You transform your appearance.
You decide what you look like, including your height,
weight, facial features, sound of your voice, hair length,
coloration, and distinguishing characteristics, if any.
You can make yourself appear as a member of another
race, though none of your statistics change. You also
can’t appear as a creature of a different size than you,
and your basic shape stays the same; if you're bipedal,
you can’t use this spell to become quadrupedal, for
instance. At any time for the duration of the spell, you
can use your action to change your appearance in
this way again.

Natural Weapons. You grow claws, fangs, spines,
horns, or a different natural w eapon of your choice. Your
unarmed strikes deal 1d6 bludgeoning, piercing, or
slashing damage, as appropriate to the natural weapon
you chose, and you are proficient with your unarmed
strikes. Finally, the natural weapon is magic and you
have a +1 bonus to the attack and damage rolls you
make using it.</Description>
    <ItemName>Alter Self</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Alter Self</SpellName>
    <School>Transmutation</School>
    <SpellLevel>2</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>This spell lets you convince a beast that you mean it no
harm. Choose a beast that you can see within range.
It must see and hear you. If the beast’s Intelligence is
4 or higher, the spell fails. Otherwise, the beast must
succeed on a W isdom saving throw or be charmed
by you for the spell’s duration. If you or one of your
companions harms the target, the spells ends.</Description>
    <ItemName>Animal Friendship</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Animal Friendship</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using
a spell slot o f 2nd level or higher, you can affect one
additional beast for each slot level above 1st.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Enchantment</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>14400</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>A morsel of food</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>By means of this spell, you use an animal to deliver a
message. Choose a Tiny beast you can see within range,
such as a squirrel, a blue jay, or a bat. You specify a
location, which you must have visited, and a recipient
who matches a general description, such as “a man or
woman dressed in the uniform of the town guard” or “a
red-haired dwarf wearing a pointed hat.” You also speak
a message of up to twenty-five words. The target beast
travels for the duration of the spell toward the specified
location, covering about 50 miles per 24 hours for a
flying messenger, or 25 miles for other animals.

When the messenger arrives, it delivers your m essage
to the creature that you described, replicating the sound
o f your voice. The messenger speaks only to a creature
matching the description you gave. If the messenger
doesn’t reach its destination before the spell ends, the
message is lost, and the beast makes its way back to
where you cast this spell.</Description>
    <ItemName>Animal Messenger</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Animal Messenger</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>If you cast this spell using a spell
slot of 3nd level or higher, the duration of the spell
increases by 48 hours for each slot level above 2nd.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Enchantment</School>
    <SpellLevel>2</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>14400</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>true</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>A morsel of food</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Your magic turns others into beasts. Choose any
number of willing creatures that you can see within
range. You transform each target into the form of a
Large or smaller beast with a challenge rating of 4 or
lower. 

On subsequent turns, you can use your action to
transform affected creatures into new forms.
The transformation lasts for the duration for each
target, or until the target drops to 0 hit points or dies.
You can choose a different form for each target. 

A target’s game statistics are replaced by the statistics o f
the chosen beast, though the target retains its alignment
and Intelligence, Wisdom, and Charisma scores. The
target assumes the hit points o f its new form, and when
it reverts to its normal form, it returns to the number
o f hit points it had before it transformed. If it reverts as
a result o f dropping to 0 hit points, any excess damage
carries over to its normal form. As long as the excess
damage doesn’t reduce the creature’s normal form to 0
hit points, it isn’t knocked unconscious. 

The creature is limited in the actions it can perform by the nature of its
new form, and it can’t speak or cast spells.

The target’s gear melds into the new form. The target
can’t activate, wield, or otherwise benefit from any of its equipment.</Description>
    <ItemName>Animal Shapes</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Animal Shapes</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Transmutation</School>
    <SpellLevel>8</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>14400</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>This spell creates an undead servant. Choose a pile
of bones or a corpse o f a Medium or Small humanoid
within range. Your spell imbues the target with a foul
mimicry of life, raising it as an undead creature. The
target becomes a skeleton if you chose bones or a
zombie if you chose a corpse (the DM has the creature’s
game statistics).

On each of your turns, you can use a bonus action
to mentally command any creature you made with
this spell if the creature is within 60 feet of you (if you
control multiple creatures, you can command any or all
of them at the same time, issuing the same command to
each one). You decide what action the creature will take
and where it w ill move during its next turn, or you can
issue a general command, such as to guard a particular
chamber or corridor. If you issue no commands, the
creature only defends itself against hostile creatures.
Once given an order, the creature continues to follow it
until its task is complete.

The creature is under your control for 24 hours,
after which it stops obeying any command you’ve given
it. To maintain control of the creature for another
24 hours, you must cast this spell on the creature
again before the current 24-hour period ends. This
use of the spell reasserts your control over up to four
creatures you have animated with this spell, rather than
animating a new one.</Description>
    <ItemName>Animate Dead</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Animate Dead</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a
spell slot of 4th level or higher, you animate or reassert
control over two additional undead creatures for each
slot level above 3rd. Each o f the creatures must come
from a different corpse or pile of bones.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Necromancy</School>
    <SpellLevel>3</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>10</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>10</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a drop of blood, a piece of flesh,</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Objects come to life at your command. Choose up to
ten nonmagical objects within range that are not being
worn or carried. Medium targets count as two objects,
Large targets count as four objects, Huge targets
count as eight objects. You can’t animate any object
larger than Huge. Each target animates and becomes a
creature under your control until the spell ends or until
reduced to 0 hit points.

As a bonus action, you can mentally command any
creature you made with this spell if the creature is
within 500 feet of you (if you control multiple creatures,
you can command any or all o f them at the same time,
issuing the same command to each one). You decide
what action the creature w ill take and where it will
move during its next turn, or you can issue a general
command, such as to guard a particular chamber or
corridor. If you issue no commands, the creature only
defends itself against hostile creatures. Once given
an order, the creature continues to follow it until its
task is complete.

A n i m a t e d  O b j e c t  S t a t i s t i c s
Size      HP    AC     Attack                         Str Dex
Tiny       20    18    +8 to hit, 1d4 + 4 damage   4   18
Small     25    16    +6 to hit, 1d8 + 2 damage    6   14
Medium  40    13    +5 to hit, 2d6 + 1 damage  10   12
Large      50    10    +6 to hit, 2d10 + 2 damage 14  10
Huge      80    10    +8 to hit, 2d12 + 4 damage 18   6

An animated object is a construct with AC, hit points,
attacks, Strength, and Dexterity determined by its size.
Its Constitution is 10 and its Intelligence and Wisdom
are 3, and its Charisma is 1. Its speed is 30 feet; if the
object lacks legs or other appendages it can use for
locomotion, it instead has a flying speed o f 30 feet and
can hover. If the object is securely attached to a surface
or a larger object, such as a chain bolted to a wall, its
speed is 0. It has blindsight with a radius o f 30 feet and
is blind beyond that distance. When the animated object
drops to 0 hit points, it reverts to its original object
form, and any remaining damage carries over to its
original object form.

If you command an object to attack, it can make a
single melee attack against a creature within 5 feet
of it. It makes a slam attack with an attack bonus and
bludgeoning damage determined by its size. The DM
might rule that a specific object inflicts slashing or
piercing damage based on its form.</Description>
    <ItemName>Animate Objects</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Animate Objects</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>If you cast this spell using a spell slot of 
6th level or higher, you can animate two
additional objects for each slot level above 5th.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Transmutation</School>
    <SpellLevel>5</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>120</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>A shimmering barrier extends out from you in a 10-foot
radius and moves with you, remaining centered on
you and hedging out creatures other than undead and
constructs. The barrier lasts for the duration.
The barrier prevents an affected creature from
passing or reaching through. An affected creature
can cast spells or make attacks with ranged or reach
weapons through the barrier.

If you move so that an affected creature is forced to
pass through the barrier, the spell ends.</Description>
    <ItemName>Antilife Shell</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Antilife Shell</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Abjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>5</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>10</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>A 10-foot-radius invisible sphere o f antimagic surrounds
you. This area is divorced from the magical energy that
suffuses the multiverse. Within the sphere, spells can’t
be cast, summoned creatures disappear, and even m agic
items become mundane. Until the spell ends, the sphere
moves with you, centered on you.
Spells and other magical effects, except those created
by an artifact or a deity, are suppressed in the sphere
and can’t protrude into it. A slot expended to cast
a suppressed spell is consumed. While an effect is
suppressed, it doesn’t function, but the time it spends
suppressed counts against its duration.

Targeted Effects. Spells and other magical effects,
such as magic missile and charm person, that target
a creature or an object in the sphere have no effect
on that target.

Areas o f Magic. The area o f another spell or magical
effect, such as fireball, can’t extend into the sphere.
If the sphere overlaps an area o f magic, the part of
the area that is covered by the sphere is suppressed.
For example, the flames created by a wall o f fire are
suppressed within the sphere, creating a gap in the wall
if the overlap is large enough.

Spells. Any active spell or other magical effect on a
creature or an object in the sphere is suppressed while
the creature or object is in it.

Magic Items. The properties and powers of
magic items are suppressed in the sphere. For
example, a + 1 longsword in the sphere functions as a
nonmagical longsword.
A magic weapon’s properties and powers are
suppressed if it is used against a target in the sphere or
wielded by an attacker in the sphere. If a magic w eapon
or a piece o f magic ammunition fully leaves the sphere
(for example, if you fire a magic arrow or throw a magic
spear at a target outside the sphere), the magic o f the
item ceases to be suppressed as soon as it exits.

Magical Travel. Teleportation and planar travel
fail to work in the sphere, whether the sphere is the
destination or the departure point for such magical
travel. A portal to another location, world, or plane of
existence, as w ell as an opening to an extradimensional
space such as that created by the rope trick spell,
temporarily closes while in the sphere.

Creatures and Objects. A creature or object
summoned or created by m agic temporarily winks out
o f existence in the sphere. Such a creature instantly
reappears once the space the creature occupied is no
longer within the sphere.

Dispel Magic. Spells and magical effects such as
dispel magic have no effect on the sphere. Likewise, the
spheres created by different antimagic field spells don’t
nullify each other.</Description>
    <ItemName>Antimagic Field</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Antimagic Field</SpellName>
    <School>Abjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>8</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>10</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_SPHERE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a pinch of powdered iron or iron filings</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>This spell attracts or repels creatures of your choice.
You target something within range, either a Huge or
smaller object or creature or an area that is no larger
than a 200-foot cube. Then specify a kind of intelligent
creature, such as red dragons, goblins, or vampires.
You invest the target with an aura that either attracts or
repels the specified creatures for the duration. Choose
antipathy or sympathy as the aura’s effect.

Antipathy. The enchantment causes creatures of the
kind you designated to feel an intense urge to leave the
area and avoid the target. When such a creature can
see the target or comes within 60 feet of it, the creature
must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or become
frightened. The creature remains frightened while it can
see the target or is within 60 feet of it. While frightened
by the target, the creature must use its movement to move to the nearest 
safe spot from which it can’t see the target. If the creature moves more than 
60 feet from the target and can’t see it, the creature is no longer
frightened, but the creature becomes frightened again if
it regains sight o f the target or moves within 60 feet of it.

Sympathy. The enchantment causes the specified
creatures to feel an intense urge to approach the target
while within 60 feet of it or able to see it. When such a
creature can see the target or comes within 60 feet o f it,
the creature must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or
use its movement on each o f its turns to enter the area
or move within reach of the target. When the creature
has done so, it can’t willingly m ove away from the target.
If the target damages or otherwise harms an affected
creature, the affected creature can make a Wisdom
saving throw to end the effect, as described below.

Ending the Effect. If an affected creature ends its
turn while not within 60 feet of the target or able to see
it, the creature makes a Wisdom saving throw. On a
successful save, the creature is no longer affected by
the target and recognizes the feeling of repugnance or
attraction as magical. In addition, a creature affected by
the spell is allowed another Wisdom saving throw every
24 hours while the spell persists.

A creature that successfully saves against this effect
is immune to it for 1 minute, after which time it can be
affected again.</Description>
    <ItemName>Antipathy/Sympathy</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Antipathy/Sympathy</SpellName>
    <School>Enchantment</School>
    <SpellLevel>8</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>144000</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>600</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>either a lump of alum soaked in vinegar for the antipathy effect or a drop of honey for the sympathy effect</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You create an invisible, magical eye within range that
hovers in the air for the duration.
You mentally receive visual information from the eye,
which has normal vision and darkvision out to 30 feet.

The eye can look in every direction.
As an action, you can move the eye up to 30 feet in
any direction. There is no limit to how far away from
you the eye can move, but it can’t enter another plane
of existence. A solid barrier blocks the eye’s movement,
but the eye can pass through an opening as small as 1
inch in diameter.</Description>
    <ItemName>Arcane Eye</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Arcane Eye</SpellName>
    <School>Divination</School>
    <SpellLevel>4</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a bit of bat fur</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You create linked teleportation portals that remain open
for the duration. Choose two points on the ground that
you can see, one point within 10 feet of you and one
point within 500 feet of you. A circular portal, 10 feet
in diameter, opens over each point. If the portal would
open in the space occupied by a creature, the spell fails,
and the casting is lost.

The portals are two-dimensional glowing rings
filled with mist, hovering inches from the ground and p
erpendicular to it at the points you choose. A ring is
visible only from one side (your choice), which is the side
that functions as a portal.

Any creature or object entering the portal exits from
the other portal as if the two were adjacent to each
other; passing through a portal from the nonportal side
has no effect. The mist that fills each portal is opaque
and blocks vision through it. On your turn, you can
rotate the rings as a bonus action so that the active side
faces in a different direction.</Description>
    <ItemName>Arcane Gate</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Arcane Gate</SpellName>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>6</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>500</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>100</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You touch a closed door, window, gate, chest, or other
entryway, and it becomes locked for the duration. You
and the creatures you designate when you cast this
spell can open the object normally. You can also set a
password that, when spoken within 5 feet of the object,
suppresses this spell for 1 minute. Otherwise, it is
impassable until it is broken or the spell is dispelled or
suppressed. Casting knock on the object suppresses
arcane lock for 10 minutes.

While affected by this spell, the object is more difficult
to break or force open; the DC to break it or pick any
locks on it increases by 10.</Description>
    <ItemName>Arcane Lock</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Arcane Lock</SpellName>
    <School>Abjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>2</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>gold dust worth at least 25gp, which the spell consumes</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>25</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>A protective magical force surrounds you, manifesting
as a spectral frost that covers you and your gear.
You gain 5 temporary hit points for the duration. If a
creature hits you with a melee attack while you have
these hit points, the creature takes 5 cold damage.</Description>
    <ItemName>Armor of Agathys</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Armor of Agathys</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a spell slot o f 2nd level or higher, 
both the temporary hit points and the cold damage increase by 
5 for each slot level above 1st.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Abjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a cup of water</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You invoke the power of Hadar, the Dark Hunger.
Tendrils of dark energy erupt from you and batter all
creatures within 10 feet of you. Each creature in that
area must m ake a Strength saving throw. On a failed
save, a target takes 2d6 necrotic damage and can’t take
reactions until its next turn. On a successful save, the
creature takes half damage, but suffers no other effect.</Description>
    <ItemName>Arms of Hadar</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Arms of Hadar</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a
spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by
1d6 for each slot level above 1st.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>10</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_SPHERE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You and up to eight willing creatures within range
project your astral bodies into the Astral Plane (the
spell fails and the casting is wasted if you are already
on that plane). The material body you leave behind is
unconscious and in a state of suspended animation; it
doesn’t need food or air and doesn’t age.

Your astral body resembles your m rtal form in
almost every way, replicating your game statistics and
possessions. The principal difference is the addition of
a silvery cord that extends from between your shoulder
blades and trails behind you, fading to invisibility after
1 foot. This cord is your tether to your material body. As
long as the tether remains intact, you can find your way
home. If the cord is cut—something that can happen
only when an effect specifically states that it does—your
soul and body are separated, killing you instantly.

Your astral form can freely travel through the Astral
Plane and can pass through portals there leading to any
other plane. If you enter a new plane or return to the
plane you were on when casting this spell, your body and
possessions are transported along the silver cord, allowing
you to re-enter your body as you enter the new plane.
Your astral form is a separate incarnation. Any damage
or other effects that apply to it have no effect on your
physical body, nor do they persist when you return to it.
The spell ends for you and your companions when
you use your action to dismiss it. When the spell ends,
the affected creature returns to its physical body,
and it awakens.

The spell might also end early for you or one of your
companions. A successful dispel magic spell used
against an astral or physical body ends the spell for that
creature. If a creature’s original body or its astral form
drops to 0 hit points, the spell ends for that creature. If
the spell ends and the silver cord is intact, the cord pulls
the creature’s astral form back to its body, ending its
state of suspended animation.
If you are returned to your body prematurely, your
companions remain in their astral forms and must find
their own way back to their bodies, usually by dropping
to 0 hit points.</Description>
    <ItemName>Astral Projection</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Astral Projection</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Necromancy</School>
    <SpellLevel>9</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>10</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>600</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>for each creature you affect with this spell, you must provide one jacinth worth at least 1000GP and one ornately carved bar of silver worth at least 100gp, all of which the spell consumes</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>1100</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>By casting gem-inlaid sticks, rolling dragon bones,
laying out ornate cards, or employing some other
divining tool, you receive an omen from an otherworldly
entity about the results o f a specific course o f action that
you plan to take within the next 30 minutes. The DM
chooses from the following possible omens:

-&gt;Weal, for good results
-&gt;Woe, for bad results
-&gt;Weal and woe, for both good and bad results
-&gt;Nothing, for results that aren’t especially good or bad

The spell doesn’t take into account any possible
circumstances that might change the outcome, such
as the casting o f additional spells or the loss or gain
of a companion.

If you cast the spell two or more times before
completing your next long rest, there is a cumulative 25
percent chance for each casting after the first that you
get a random reading. The DM makes this roll in secret.</Description>
    <ItemName>Augury</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Augury</SpellName>
    <School>Divination</School>
    <SpellLevel>2</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>10</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>true</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>specially marked sticks, bones,or similar tokens w orth at least 25 gp</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>25</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Life-preserving energy radiates from you in an aura with
a 30-foot radius. Until the spell ends, the aura moves
with you, centered on you. Each nonhostile creature
in the aura (including you) has resistance to necrotic
damage, and its hit point maximum can't be reduced. In
addition, a nonhostile, living creature regains 1 hit point
when it starts its turn in the aura with 0 hit points.</Description>
    <ItemName>Aura Of Life</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Aura Of Life</SpellName>
    <School>Abjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>4</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>100</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>30</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_SPHERE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>false</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Purifying energy radiates from you in an aura with a
30-foot radius. Until the spell ends, the aura moves
with you, centered on you. Each nonhostile creature
in the aura (including you) can’t become diseased,
has resistance to poison damage, and has advantage
on saving throws against effects that cause any of the
following conditions: blinded, charmed, deafened,
frightened, paralyzed, poisoned, and stunned.</Description>
    <ItemName>Aura Of Purity</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Aura Of Purity</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Abjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>4</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>100</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>30</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_SPHERE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>false</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Healing energy radiates from you in an aura with a
30-foot radius. Until the spell ends, the aura moves with
you, centered on you. You can use a bonus action to
cause one creature in the aura (including you) to regain
2d6 hit points.</Description>
    <ItemName>Aura Of Vitality</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Aura Of Vitality</SpellName>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>3</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>30</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_SPHERE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>false</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>After spending the casting time tracing magical
pathways within a precious gemstone, you touch a Huge
or smaller beast or plant. The target must have either
no Intelligence score or an Intelligence o f 3 or less. The
target gains an Intelligence o f 10. The target also gains
the ability to speak one language you know. If the target
is a plant, it gains the ability to move its limbs, roots,
vines, creepers, and so forth, and it gains senses similar
to a human’s. Your DM chooses statistics appropriate
for the awakened plant, such as the statistics for the
awakened shrub or the awakened tree.

The awakened beast or plant is charmed by you for
30 days or until you or your companions do anything
harmful to it. When the charmed condition ends,
the awakened creature chooses whether to remain
friendly to you, based on how you treated it while
it w as charmed.</Description>
    <ItemName>Awaken</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Awaken</SpellName>
    <School>Transmutation</School>
    <SpellLevel>5</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>4800</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>an agate worth at least 1,000 gp, which the spell consumes</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>1000</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Up to three creatures o f your choice that you can see
within range must make Charisma saving throws.
Whenever a target that fails this saving throw makes
an attack roll or a saving throw before the spell ends,
the target must roll a d4 and subtract the number rolled
from the attack roll or saving throw.</Description>
    <ItemName>Bane</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Bane</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using
a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one
additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Enchantment</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a drop of blood</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>The next time you hit a creature with a weapon attack
before this spell ends, your weapon crackles with force,
and the attack deals an extra 5d10 force damage to the
target. Additionally, if this attack reduces the target
to 50 hit points or fewer, you banish it. If the target is
native to a different plane of existence than the one
you’re on, the target disappears, returning to its home
plane. If the target is native to the plane you’re on, the
creature vanishes into a harmless demiplane. While
there, the target is incapacitated. It remains there until
the spell ends, at which point the target reappears in the
space it left or in the nearest unoccupied space if that
space is occupied.</Description>
    <ItemName>Banishing Smite</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Banishing Smite</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Abjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>5</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_BONUS_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>false</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You attempt to send one creature that you can see
within range to another plane of existence. The
target must succeed on a Charisma saving throw
or be banished.

If the target is native to the plane of existence you’re
on, you banish the target to a harmless demiplane.
While there, the target is incapacitated. The target
remains there until the spell ends, at which point the
target reappears in the space it left or in the nearest
unoccupied space if that space is occupied.
If the target is native to a different plane of existence
than the one you’re on, the target is banished with
a faint popping noise, returning to its home plane.
If the spell ends before 1 minute has passed, the
target reappears in the space it left or in the nearest
unoccupied space if that space is occupied. Otherwise,
the target doesn't return.</Description>
    <ItemName>Banishment</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Banishment</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using
a spell slot of 5th level or higher, you can target one
additional creature for each slot level above 4th.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Abjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>4</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>an item distasteful to the target</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You touch a w illing creature. Until the spell ends, the
target’s skin has a rough, bark-like appearance, and the
target’s AC can’t be less than 16, regardless of what kind
of armor it is wearing.</Description>
    <ItemName>Barkskin</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Barkskin</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Transmutation</School>
    <SpellLevel>2</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a handful of oak bark</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>This spell bestows hope and vitality. Choose any
number of creatures within range. For the duration,
each target has advantage on Wisdom saving throws
and death saving throws, and regains the maximum
number of hit points possible from any healing.</Description>
    <ItemName>Beacon Of Hope</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Beacon Of Hope</SpellName>
    <School>Abjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>3</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You touch a willing beast. For the duration o f the spell,
you can use your action to see through the beast’s eyes
and hear what it hears, and continue to do so until
you use your action to return to your normal senses.

While perceiving through the beast’s senses, you gain
the benefits of any special senses possessed by that
creature, though you are blinded and deafened to your
own surroundings.</Description>
    <ItemName>Beast Sense</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Beast Sense</SpellName>
    <School>Divination</School>
    <SpellLevel>2</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>false</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>true</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You touch a creature, and that creature must succeed
on a W isdom saving throw or become cursed for the
duration o f the spell. When you cast this spell, choose
the nature o f the curse from the following options:

-&gt; Choose one ability score. While cursed, the target
has disadvantage on ability checks and saving throws
made with that ability score.

-&gt;While cursed, the target has disadvantage on attack
rolls against you.

-&gt;While cursed, the target must make a W isdom saving
throw at the start o f each o f its turns. If it fails, it
wastes its action that turn doing nothing.

-&gt;While the target is cursed, your attacks and spells
deal an extra 1d8 necrotic damage to the target.

A remove curse spell ends this effect. At the DM’s
option, you may choose an alternative curse effect, but
it should be no more powerful than those described
above. The DM has final say on such a curse’s effect.</Description>
    <ItemName>Bestow Curse</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Bestow Curse</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>If you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th level or higher, 
the duration is concentration, up to 10 minutes. 
If you use a spell slot of 5th level or higher, the duration is 8 hours. 
If you use a spell slot of 7th level or higher, the duration is 24 hours. 
If you use a 9th level spell slot, the spell lasts until it is dispelled.
Using a spell slot o f 5th level or higher grants a duration
that doesn’t require concentration.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Necromancy</School>
    <SpellLevel>3</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You create a Large hand of shimmering, translucent force in an 
unoccupied space that you can see within range. The hand lasts 
for the spell’s duration, and it moves at your command, mimicking 
the movements of your own hand.

The hand is an object that has AC 20 and hit points equal to your hit point
 maximum. If it drops to 0 hit points, the spell ends. It has a Strength of 
26 (+8) and a Dexterity o f 10 (+0). The hand doesn’t fill its space.
When you cast the spell and as a bonus action on your subsequent turns, 
you can move the hand up to 60 feet and then cause one of the following 
effects with it.

Clenched Fist -&gt; The hand strikes one creature or
object within 5 feet o f it. Make a melee spell attack for
the hand using your game statistics. On a hit, the target
takes 4d8 force damage.

Forceful Hand -&gt; The hand attempts to push a creature
within 5 feet of it in a direction you choose. Make
a check with the hand’s Strength contested by the
Strength (Athletics) check of the target. If the target is
Medium or smaller, you have advantage on the check. If
you succeed, the hand pushes the target up to 5 feet plus
a number of feet equal to five times your spellcasting
ability modifier. The hand moves with the target to
remain within 5 feet of it.

Grasping Hand -&gt; The hand attempts to grapple a Huge
or smaller creature within 5 feet of it. You use the hand’s
Strength score to resolve the grapple. If the target is
Medium or smaller, you have advantage on the check.
While the hand is grappling the target, you can use a
bonus action to have the hand crush it. When you do
so, the target takes bludgeoning damage equal to 2d6 +
your spellcasting ability modifier.

Interposing Hand -&gt; The hand interposes itself
between you and a creature you choose until you give
the hand a different command. The hand moves to stay
between you and the target, providing you with half
cover against the target. The target can't move through
the hand’s space if its Strength score is less than or
equal to the hand’s Strength score. If its Strength score
is higher than the hand’s Strength score, the target can
move toward you through the hand’s space, but that
space is difficult terrain for the target.

</Description>
    <ItemName>Bigby's Hand</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Bigby's Hand</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a
spell slot of 6th level or higher, the damage from the
clenched fist option increases by 2d8 and the damage
from the grasping hand increases by 2d6 for each slot
level above 5th.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>5</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>120</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>an eggshell and a snakeskin glove</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You create a vertical wall of whirling, razor-sharp blades
made of magical energy. The wall appears within range
and lasts for the duration. You can make a straight wall
up to 100 feet long, 20 feet high, and 5 feet thick, or a
ringed wall up to 60 feet in diameter, 20 feet high, and
5 feet thick. 

The wall provides three-quarters cover to
creatures behind it, and its space is difficult terrain.
When a creature enters the w all’s area for the first
time on a turn or starts its turn there, the creature must
make a Dexterity saving throw. On a failed save, the
creature takes 6 d10 slashing damage. On a successful
save, the creature takes half as much damage.</Description>
    <ItemName>Blade Barrier</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Blade Barrier</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>6</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>90</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>100</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You extend your hand and trace a sigil of warding in the
air. Until the end of your next turn, you have resistance
against bludgeoning, piercing, and slashing damage
dealt by weapon attacks.</Description>
    <ItemName>Blade Ward</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Blade Ward</SpellName>
    <School>Abjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You bless up to three creatures of your choice within
range. Whenever a target makes an attack roll or a
saving throw before the spell ends, the target can roll
a d4 and add the number rolled to the attack roll or
saving throw.</Description>
    <ItemName>Bless</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Bless</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd 
level or higher, you can target one additional 
creature for each slot level above 1st.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Enchantment</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a sprinkling of holy water</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Necromantic energy washes over a creature of your
choice that you can see within range, draining moisture
and vitality from it. The target must make a Constitution
saving throw. The target takes 8d8 necrotic damage on
a failed save, or half as much damage on a successful
one. This spell has no effect on undead or constructs.
If you target a plant creature or a magical plant, it
makes the saving throw with disadvantage, and the spell
deals maximum damage to it.
If you target a nonmagical plant that isn’t a creature,
such as a tree or shrub, it doesn’t make a saving throw;
it simply withers and dies.</Description>
    <ItemName>Blight</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Blight</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a
spell slot o f 5th level or higher, the damage increases by
1d8 for each slot level above 4th.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Necromancy</School>
    <SpellLevel>4</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>The next time you hit a creature with a melee w eapon
attack during this spell’s duration, your weapon flares
with bright light, and the attack deals an extra 3d8
radiant damage to the target. Additionally, the target
must succeed on a Constitution saving throw or be
blinded until the spell ends.

A creature blinded by this spell makes another
Constitution saving throw at the end o f each o f its turns.
On a successful save, it is no longer blinded.</Description>
    <ItemName>Blinding Smite</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Blinding Smite</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>3</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>false</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You can blind or deafen a foe. Choose one creature that
you can see within range to make a Constitution saving
throw. If it fails, the target is either blinded or deafened
(your choice) for the duration. At the end of each of its
turns, the target can make a Constitution saving throw.
On a success, the spell ends.</Description>
    <ItemName>Blindness/Deafness</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Blindness/Deafness</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a spell slot o f 3rd level 
or higher, you can target one additional creature for 
each slot level above 2nd.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Necromancy</School>
    <SpellLevel>2</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>false</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Roll a d20 at the end of each o f your turns for the
duration of the spell. On a roll o f 11 or higher, you
vanish from your current plane of existence and appear
in the Ethereal Plane (the spell fails and the casting is
wasted if you were already on that plane). At the start of
your next turn, and when the spell ends if you are on the
Ethereal Plane, you return to an unoccupied space of
your choice that you can see within 10 feet of the space
you vanished from. If no unoccupied space is available
within that range, you appear in the nearest unoccupied
space (chosen at random if more than one space is
equally near). You can dismiss this spell as an action.

While on the Ethereal Plane, you can see and hear
the plane you originated from, which is cast in shades
of gray, and you can’t see anything there more than 60
feet away. You can only affect and be affected by other
creatures on the Ethereal Plane. Creatures that aren’t
there can’t perceive you or interact with you, unless they
have the ability to do so.</Description>
    <ItemName>Blink</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Blink</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Transmutation</School>
    <SpellLevel>3</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Your body becomes blurred, shifting and wavering to
all w ho can see you. For the duration, any creature has
disadvantage on attack rolls against you. An attacker
is immune to this effect if it doesn’t rely on sight,
as with blindsight, or can see through illusions, as
with truesight.</Description>
    <ItemName>Blur</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Blur</SpellName>
    <School>Illusion</School>
    <SpellLevel>2</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>false</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>The next time you hit a creature with a weapon attack
before this spell ends, the w eapon gleams with astral
radiance as you strike. The attack deals an extra 2d6
radiant damage to the target, which becomes visible if
it’s invisible, and the target sheds dim light in a 5-foot
radius and can’t become invisible until the spell ends.

</Description>
    <ItemName>Branding Smite</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Branding Smite</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 3rd level 
or higher, the extra damage increases by 1d6 for 
each slot level above 2nd.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>2</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_BONUS_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>false</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>As you hold your hands with thumbs touching and fingers spread, 
a thin sheet of flames shoots forth from your outstretched fingertips. 
Each creature in a 15-foot cone must make a Dexterity saving throw. 
A creature takes 3d6 fire damage on a failed save, or half as much
damage on a successful one. The fire ignites any flammable objects in 
the area that aren’t being worn or carried.</Description>
    <ItemName>Burning Hands</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Burning Hands</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, 
the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 1st.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>15</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_CONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>A storm cloud appears in the shape of a cylinder that
is 10 feet tall with a 60-foot radius, centered on a point
you can see 100 feet directly above you. The spell fails
if you can’t see a point in the air where the storm cloud
could appear (for example, if you are in a room that can’t
accommodate the cloud).

When you cast the spell, choose a point you can see
within range. A bolt o f lightning flashes down from the
cloud to that point. Each creature within 5 feet o f that
point must make a Dexterity saving throw. A creature
takes 3d10 lightning damage on a failed save, or half
as much damage on a successful one. On each o f your
turns until the spell ends, you can use your action to call
down lightning in this way again, targeting the same
point or a different one.

If you are outdoors in stormy conditions when you
cast this spell, the spell gives you control over the
existing storm instead of creating a new one. Under
such conditions, the spell’s damage increases by 1d10.</Description>
    <ItemName>Call Lightning</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Call Lightning</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 4th or 
higher level, the damage increases by 1d10 for each 
slot level above 3rd.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>3</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>120</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>100</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You attempt to suppress strong emotions in a group
of people. Each humanoid in a 20-foot-radius sphere
centered on a point you choose within range must make
a Charisma saving throw; a creature can choose to
fail this saving throw if it w ishes. If a creature fails its
saving throw, choose one o f the following two effects.
You can suppress any effect causing a target to be
charmed or frightened. When this spell ends, any
suppressed effect resumes, provided that its duration
has not expired in the meantime.

Alternatively, you can make a target indifferent about
creatures of your choice that it is hostile toward. This
indifference ends if the target is attacked or harmed by
a spell or if it w itnesses any of its friends being harmed.
When the spell ends, the creature becomes hostile
again, unless the DM rules otherwise.</Description>
    <ItemName>Calm Emotions</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Calm Emotions</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Enchantment</School>
    <SpellLevel>2</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You create a bolt of lightning that arcs toward a target of
your choice that you can see within range. Three bolts
then leap from that target to as many as three other
targets, each o f which must be within 30 feet o f the first
target. A target can be a creature or an object and can
be targeted by only one of the bolts.

A target must make a Dexterity saving throw. The
target takes 10d8 lightning damage on a failed save, or
half as much damage on a successful one.</Description>
    <ItemName>Chain Lightning</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Chain Lightning</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using
a spell slot of 7th level or higher, one additional bolt
leaps from the first target to another target for each slot
level above 6th.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>6</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>150</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a bit of fur; a piece of amber,glass, or a crystal rod; and three silver pins</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You attempt to charm a humanoid you can see within
range. It must make a Wisdom saving throw, and does
so with advantage if you or your companions are fighting
it. If it fails the saving throw, it is charmed by you until
the spell ends or until you or your companions do
anything harmful to it. The charmed creature regards
you as a friendly acquaintance. When the spell ends, the
creature knows it was charmed by you.</Description>
    <ItemName>Charm Person</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Charm Person</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using
a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one
additional creature for each slot level above 1st. The
creatures must be within 30 feet of each other when
you target them.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Enchantment</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You create a ghostly, skeletal hand in the space of a
creature within range. Make a ranged spell attack
against the creature to assail it with the chill of the
grave. On a hit, the target takes 1d8 necrotic damage,
and it can’t regain hit points until the start of your next
turn. Until then, the hand clings to the target.
If you hit an undead target, it also has disadvantage on
attack rolls against you until the end of your next turn.
This spell’s damage increases by 1d8 when you reach
5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).</Description>
    <ItemName>Chill Touch</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Chill Touch</SpellName>
    <School>Necromancy</School>
    <SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>120</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_NONE</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You hurl a 4-inch-diameter sphere of energy at a
creature that you can see within range. You choose
acid, cold, fire, lightning, poison, or thunder for the type
of orb you create, and then make a ranged spell attack
against the target. If the attack hits, the creature takes
3d8 damage of the type you chose.</Description>
    <ItemName>Chromatic Orb</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Chromatic Orb</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a
spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by
1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>90</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a diamond worth at least 50 gp</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>sphere o f negative energy ripples out in a 60-footradius
sphere from a point within range. Each creature
in that area must make a Constitution saving throw. A
target takes 8d6 necrotic damage on a failed save, or
half as much damage on a successful one.</Description>
    <ItemName>Circle Of Death</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Circle Of Death</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 7th level
 or higher, the damage increases by 2d6 for each 
slot level above 6th.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Necromancy</School>
    <SpellLevel>6</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>150</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>60</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_SPHERE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>the powder o f a crushed black pearl worth at least 500gp</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>500</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Divine energy radiates from you, distorting and
diffusing magical energy within 30 feet o f you. Until
the spell ends, the sphere moves with you, centered on
you. For the duration, each friendly creature in the area
(including you) has advantage on saving throws against
spells and other magical effects. Additionally, when
an affected creature succeeds on a saving throw made
against a spell or magical effect that allows it to make a
saving throw to take only half damage, it instead takes
no damage if it succeeds on the saving throw.</Description>
    <ItemName>Circle Of Power</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Circle Of Power</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Abjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>5</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>100</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>30</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_SPHERE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>false</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You create an invisible sensor within range in a location
familiar to you (a place you have visited or seen before)
or in an obvious location that is unfamiliar to you (such
as behind a door, around a corner, or in a grove o f trees).
The sensor remains in place for the duration, and it
can’t be attacked or otherwise interacted with.

When you cast the spell, you choose seeing or
hearing. You can use the chosen sense through the
sensor as if you were in its space. A s your action, you
can switch between seeing and hearing.

A creature that can see the sensor (such as a creature
benefiting from see invisibility or truesight) sees a
luminous, intangible orb about the size of your fist.</Description>
    <ItemName>Clairvoyance</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Clairvoyance</SpellName>
    <School>Divination</School>
    <SpellLevel>3</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>5280</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>100</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>100</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a focus worth at least 100 gp, either a jeweled horn for hearing or a glass eye for seeing</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>100</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>This spell grows an inert duplicate o f a living creature
as a safeguard against death. This clone forms inside
a sealed vessel and grows to full size and maturity
after 120 days; you can also choose to have the clone
be a younger version o f the same creature. It remains
inert and endures indefinitely, as long as its vessel
remains undisturbed.

At any time after the clone matures, if the original
creature dies, its soul transfers to the clone, provided
that the soul is free and willing to return. The clone is
physically identical to the original and has the same
personality, memories, and abilities, but none of the
original’s equipment. The original creature’s physical
remains, if they still exist, become inert and can’t
thereafter be restored to life, since the creature’s soul
is elsewhere.</Description>
    <ItemName>Clone</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Clone</SpellName>
    <School>Necromancy</School>
    <SpellLevel>8</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>600</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>Diamond worth at least 1000gp and at least 1 cubic inch of flesh to be cloned, which the spell consumes, and a vessel worth at least 2000GP that has a sealable lid and is large enough to hold a Medium creature, such as a huge urn, coffin, mud-filled cyst in the ground or crystal container filled with salt water </MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You fill the air with spinning daggers in a cube 5 feet on
each side, centered on a point you choose within range.
A creature takes 4d4 slashing damage when it enters
the spell’s area for the first time on a turn or starts
its turn there.</Description>
    <ItemName>Cloud Of Daggers</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Cloud Of Daggers</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 
3rd level or higher, the damage increases by
2d4 for each slot level above 2nd.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>2</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a sliver of glass</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You create a 20-foot-radius sphere of poisonous, yellowgreen fog 
centered on a point you choose within range. The fog spreads around corners. 
It lasts for the duration or until strong wind disperses the fog, ending the spell.
Its area is heavily obscured.

´When a creature enters the spell’s area for the first time on a turn 
or starts its turn there, that creature must make a Constitution saving throw. 
The creature takes 5d8 poison damage on a failed save, or half as much
damage on a successful one. 

Creatures are affected even if they hold their breath or don’t need to breathe.
The fog m oves 10 feet away from you at the start of each o f your turns, rolling 
along the surface of the ground. The vapors, being heavier than air, sink to the
lowest level of the land, even pouring down openings.</Description>
    <ItemName>Cloudkill</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Cloudkill</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 6th level or higher, 
the damage increases by 1d8 for each slot level above 5th.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>5</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>120</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>100</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>20</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_SPHERE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_NONE</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>A dazzling array of flashing, colored light springs from your hand. Roll 6 d10; 
the total is how many hit points of creatures this spell can effect. Creatures 
in a 15-foot cone originating from you are affected in ascending order of 
their current hit points (ignoring unconscious creatures and creatures that can’t see).
Starting with the creature that has the lowest current hit points, each creature 
affected by this spell is blinded until the spell ends. Subtract each 
creature’s hit points from the total before moving on to the creature with
the next lowest hit points. A creature’s hit points must be equal to or 
less than the remaining total for that creature to be affected.</Description>
    <ItemName>Color Spray</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Color Spray</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a
spell slot of 2nd level or higher, roll an additional 2d10
for each slot level above 1st</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Illusion</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>15</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_CONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a pinch of powder or sand that is colored red, yellow, and blue</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You speak a one-word command to a creature you can
see within range. The target must succeed on a Wisdom
saving throw or follow the command on its next turn.
The spell has no effect if the target is undead, if it
doesn’t understand your language, or if your command
is directly harmful to it.

Some typical commands and their effects follow. You
might issue a command other than one described here.
If you do so, the DM determines how the target behaves.
If the target can’t follow your command, the spell ends.

Approach. The target moves toward you by the
shortest and most direct route, ending its turn if it
moves within 5 feet o f you.

Drop. The target drops whatever it is holding and then
ends its turn.

Flee. The target spends its turn moving away from
you by the fastest available means.

Grovel. The target falls prone and then ends its turn.

Halt. The target doesn’t move and takes no actions.
A flying creature stays aloft, provided that it is able to
do so. If it must move to stay aloft, it flies the minimum
distance needed to remain in the air.</Description>
    <ItemName>Command</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Command</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, 
you can affect one additional creature for each slot level above 1st. 
The creatures must be within 30 feet o f each other when
you target them.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Enchantment</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>false</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You contact your deity or a divine proxy and ask up to
three questions that can be answered with a yes or no.
You must ask your questions before the spell ends. You
receive a correct answer for each question.
Divine beings aren’t necessarily omniscient, so you
might receive “unclear” as an answer if a question
pertains to information that lies beyond the deity’s
knowledge. In a case where a one-word answer could be
misleading or contrary to the deity’s interests, the DM
might offer a short phrase as an answer instead.

If you cast the spell two or more times before finishing
your next long rest, there is a cumulative 25 percent
chance for each casting after the first that you get no
answer. The DM makes this roll in secret.</Description>
    <ItemName>Commune</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Commune</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Divination</School>
    <SpellLevel>5</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>10</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>true</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>incense and a vial of holy water</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You briefly become one with nature and gain knowledge
of the surrounding territory. In the outdoors, the spell
gives you knowledge o f the land within 3 miles o f you.
In caves and other natural underground settings, the
radius is limited to 300 feet. The spell doesn’t function
where nature has been replaced by construction, such
as in dungeons and towns.

You instantly gain knowledge o f up to three facts of
your choice about any o f the following subjects as they
relate to the area:

• terrain and bodies of water
• prevalent plants, minerals, animals, or peoples
• powerful celestials, fey, fiends, elementals, or undead
• influence from other planes o f existence
• buildings

For example, you could determine the location of
powerful undead in the area, the location o f major
sources of safe drinking water, and the location o f any
nearby towns.</Description>
    <ItemName>Commune With Nature</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Commune With Nature</SpellName>
    <School>Divination</School>
    <SpellLevel>5</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>10</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>true</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You attempt to compel a creature into a duel. One
creature that you can see within range must make a
Wisdom saving throw. On a failed save, the creature is
drawn to you, compelled by your divine demand. For
the duration, it has disadvantage on attack rolls against
creatures other than you, and must make a Wisdom
saving throw each time it attempts to move to a space
that is more than 30 feet away from you; if it succeeds
on this saving throw, this spell doesn’t restrict the
target’s movement for that turn.

The spell ends if you attack any other creature, if you
cast a spell that targets a hostile creature other than the
target, if a creature friendly to you damages the target or
casts a harmful spell on it, or if you end your turn more
than 30 feet away from the target.</Description>
    <ItemName>Compelled Duel</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Compelled Duel</SpellName>
    <School>Enchantment</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_BONUS_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>false</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>For the duration, you understand the literal meaning of
any spoken language that you hear. You also understand
any written language that you see, but you must be
touching the surface on which the words are written. 
It takes about 1 minute to read one page of text. This spell doesn’t 
decode secret m essages in a text or a glyph, such as an arcane sigil, 
that isn’t part of a written language</Description>
    <ItemName>Comprehend Languages</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Comprehend Languages</SpellName>
    <School>Divination</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>true</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a pinch of soot and salt</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Creatures of your choice that you can see within range
and that can hear you must make a W isdom saving
throw. A target automatically succeeds on this saving
throw if it can’t be charmed. On a failed save, a target
is affected by this spell. Until the spell ends, you can
use a bonus action on each o f your turns to designate a
direction that is horizontal to you. Each affected target
must u se as much o f its movement as possible to move
in that direction on its next turn. It can take its action
before it moves. After moving in this way, it can make
another Wisdom saving to try to end the effect.

A target isn’t compelled to move into an obviously
deadly hazard, such as a fire or pit, but it w ill provoke
opportunity attacks to move in the designated direction.</Description>
    <ItemName>Compulsion</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Compulsion</SpellName>
    <School>Enchantment</School>
    <SpellLevel>4</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>A blast o f cold air erupts from your hands. Each
creature in a 60-foot cone must make a Constitution
saving throw. A creature takes 8d8 cold damage on a
failed save, or half as much damage on a successful one.
A creature killed by this spell becomes a frozen statue
until it thaws.

</Description>
    <ItemName>Cone Of Cold</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Cone Of Cold</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a
spell slot o f 6th level or higher, the damage increases by
1d8 for each slot level above 5th.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>5</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>60</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_CONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a small crystal or glass cone</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>This spell assaults and twists creatures' minds,
spawning delusions and provoking uncontrolled action.
Each creature in a 10-foot-radius sphere centered on
a point you choose within range must succeed on a
Wisdom saving throw when you cast this spell or be
affected by it.

An affected target can’t take reactions and must roll
a d 10 at the start o f each o f its turns to determine its
behavior for that turn.

1  The creature uses all its movement to move in a
    random direction. To determine the direction, roll
    a d8 and assign a direction to each die face. The
   creature doesn’t take an action this turn.
2-6 The creature doesn’t move or take actions this turn.
7-8 The creature uses its action to make a melee attack
       against a randomly determined creature within its
       reach. If there is no creature within its reach, the
       creature does nothing this turn.
9-10 The creature can act and move normally

At the end of each of its turns, an affected target can
make a W isdom saving throw. If it succeeds, this effect
ends for that target.</Description>
    <ItemName>Confusion</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Confusion</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 
5th level or higher, the radius of the sphere increases 
by 5 feet for each slot level above 4th.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Enchantment</School>
    <SpellLevel>4</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>90</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>10</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_SPHERE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>three nut shells</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You summon fey spirits that take the form o f beasts and
appear in unoccupied spaces that you can see within
range. Choose one o f the following options for what
appears:

• One beast o f challenge rating 2 or lower
• Two beasts o f challenge rating 1 or lower
• Four beasts o f challenge rating 1/2 or lower
• Eight beasts o f challenge rating 1/4 or lower

Each beast is also considered fey, and it disappears
when it drops to 0 hit points or when the spell ends.
The summoned creatures are friendly to you and your
companions. Roll initiative for the summoned creatures
as a group, which has its own turns. They obey any
verbal commands that you issue to them (no action
required by you). If you don’t issue any commands to
them, they defend themselves from hostile creatures,
but otherwise take no actions.

The DM has the creatures’ statistics.</Description>
    <ItemName>Conjure Animals</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Conjure Animals</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using certain higher-level spell slots, 
you choose one of the summoning options above, and more creatures appear:
twice as many with a 5th-level slot, three times as many
with a 7th-level slot, and four times as many with a
9th-level slot.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>3</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You throw a nonmagical w eapon or fire a piece of
nonmagical ammunition into the air to create a cone
of identical weapons that shoot forward and then
disappear. Each creature in a 60-foot cone must succeed
on a Dexterity saving throw. A creature takes 3d8
damage on a failed save, or half as much damage on a
successful one. The damage type is the same as that of
the weapon or ammunition used as a component.</Description>
    <ItemName>Conjure Barrage</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Conjure Barrage</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>3</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>60</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_CONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>one piece of ammunition or a thrown weapon</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You summon a celestial o f challenge rating 4 or lower,
which appears in an unoccupied space that you can see
within range. The celestial disappears when it drops to
0 hit points or when the spell ends.
The celestial is friendly to you and your companions
for the duration. Roll initiative for the celestial, which
has its own turns. It obeys any verbal commands that
you issue to it (no action required by you), as long as
they don’t violate its alignment. If you don’t issue any
commands to the celestial, it defends itself from hostile
creatures but otherwise takes no actions.
The DM has the celestial’s statistics.</Description>
    <ItemName>Conjure Celestial</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Conjure Celestial</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a 9th-level spell slot, 
you summon a celestial of challenge rating 5 or lower.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>7</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>90</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>10</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You call forth an elemental servant. Choose an area o f air,
earth, fire, or water that fills a 10-foot cube within range.
An elemental o f challenge rating 5 or lower appropriate
to the area you chose appears in an unoccupied space
within 10 feet o f it. For example, a fire elemental
emerges from a bonfire, and an earth elemental rises
up from the ground. The elemental disappears when it
drops to 0 hit points or when the spell ends.
The elemental is friendly to you and your companions
for the duration. Roll initiative for the elemental, which
has its own turns. It obeys any verbal commands that
you issue to it (no action required by you). If you don’t
issue any commands to the elemental, it defends itself
from hostile creatures but otherwise takes no actions.
If your concentration is broken, the elemental doesn’t
disappear. Instead, you lose control o f the elemental,
it becomes hostile toward you and your companions,
and it might attack. An uncontrolled elemental can’t
be dismissed by you, and it disappears 1 hour after
you summoned it.

The DM has the elemental’s statistics.</Description>
    <ItemName>Conjure Elemental</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Conjure Elemental</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using
a spell slot o f 6th level or higher, the challenge rating
increases by 1 for each slot level above 5th.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>5</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>90</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>burning incense for air, soft clay for earth, sulfur and phosphorus fire, or water and sand for water</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You summon a fey creature o f challenge rating 6 or
lower, or a fey spirit that takes the form of a beast of
challenge rating 6 or lower. It appears in an unoccupied
space that you can see within range. The fey creature
disappears when it drops to 0 hit points or when
the spell ends.

The fey creature is friendly to you and your
companions for the duration. Roll initiative for the
creature, which has its own turns. It obeys any verbal
commands that you issue to it (no action required
by you), as long as they don't violate its alignment. If
you don’t issue any commands to the fey creature, it
defends itself from hostile creatures but otherwise
takes no actions.

If your concentration is broken, the fey creature
doesn’t disappear. Instead, you lose control o f the
fey creature, it becomes hostile toward you and your
companions, and it might attack. An uncontrolled fey
creature can't be dismissed by you, and it disappears 1
hour after you summoned it.
The DM has the fey creature’s statistics.</Description>
    <ItemName>Conjure Fey</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Conjure Fey</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using
a spell slot o f 7th level or higher, the challenge rating
increases by 1 for each slot level above 6th.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>6</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>90</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>10</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You summon elementals that appear in unoccupied
spaces that you can see within range. You choose one
the following options for what appears:

• One elemental o f challenge rating 2 or lower
• Two elementals o f challenge rating 1 or lower
• Four elementals o f challenge rating 1/2 or lower
• Eight elementals of challenge rating 1/4 or lower.

An elemental summoned by this spell disappears when
it drops to 0 hit points or when the spell ends.
The summoned creatures are friendly to you and your
companions. Roll initiative for the summoned creatures
as a group, which has its own turns. They obey any
verbal commands that you issue to them (no action
required by you). If you don’t issue any commands to
them, they defend themselves from hostile creatures,
but otherwise take no actions.

The DM has the creatures' statistics.</Description>
    <ItemName>Conjure Minor Elementals</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Conjure Minor Elementals</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using certain higher-level spell slots, 
you choose one of the summoning options above, and more 
creatures appear: twice as many with a 6th-level slot and three times as
many with an 8th-level slot.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>4</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>90</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You fire a piece o f nonmagical ammunition from a
ranged weapon or throw a nonmagical w eapon into
the air and choose a point within range. Hundreds of
duplicates of the ammunition or weapon fall in a volley
from above and then disappear. Each creature in a
40-foot-radius. 20-foot-high cylinder centered on that
point must make a Dexterity saving throw. A creature
takes 8d8 damage on a failed save, or half as much
damage on a successful one. The damage type is the
same as that of the ammunition or weapon.</Description>
    <ItemName>Conjure Volley</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Conjure Volley</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>5</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>150</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>one piece of ammunition or one thrown weapon</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You summon fey creatures that appear in unoccupied
spaces that you can see within range. Choose one o f the
following options for what appears:

• One fey creature o f challenge rating 2 or lower
• Two fey creatures o f challenge rating 1 or lower
• Four fey creatures o f challenge rating 1/2 or lower
• Eight fey creatures o f challenge rating 1/4 or lower

A summoned creature disappears when it drops to 0 hit
points or when the spell ends.
The summoned creatures are friendly to you and your
companions. Roll initiative for the summoned creatures
as a group, which have their own turns. They obey any
verbal commands that you issue to them (no action
required by you). If you don't issue any commands to
them, they defend themselves from hostile creatures,
but otherwise take no actions.

The DM has the creatures’ statistics.</Description>
    <ItemName>Conjure Woodland Beings</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Conjure Woodland Beings</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using certain higher-level spell slots, 
you choose one of the summoning options above, and more creatures appear:
twice as many with a 6th-level slot and three times as
many with an 8th-level slot.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>4</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>one holly berry per creature summoned</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You mentally contact a demigod, the spirit o f a long-dead
sage, or some other mysterious entity from another
plane. Contacting this extraplanar intelligence can
strain or even break your mind. When you cast this
spell, make a DC 15 Intelligence saving throw. 

On a failure, you take 6d6 psychic damage and are insane
until you finish a long rest. While insane, you can’t take
actions, can’t understand what other creatures say, can’t
read, and speak only in gibberish. A greater restoration
spell cast on you ends this effect.
On a successful save, you can ask the entity up to five
questions. You must ask your questions before the spell
ends. The DM answers each question with one word,
such as “yes,” “no,” “maybe,” “never,” “irrelevant,” or
“unclear” (if the entity doesn’t know the answer to the
question). If a one-word answer w ould be misleading,
the DM might instead offer a short phrase as an answer.</Description>
    <ItemName>Contact Other Plane</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Contact Other Plane</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Divination</School>
    <SpellLevel>5</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>10</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>false</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>true</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Your touch inflicts disease. Make a melee spell attack
against a creature within your reach. On a hit, you afflict
the creature with a disease o f your choice from any o f
the ones described below.
At the end o f each o f the target’s turns, it must make
a Constitution saving throw. After failing three of
these saving throws, the disease’s effects last for the
duration, and the creature stops making these saves.
After succeeding on three o f these saving throws, the
creature recovers from the disease, and the spell ends.
Since this spell induces a natural disease in its
target, any effect that removes a disease or otherwise
ameliorates a disease’s effects apply to it.

Blinding Sickness. Pain grips the creature’s mind,
and its eyes turn milky white. The creature has
disadvantage on Wisdom checks and W isdom saving
throws and is blinded.

Filth Fever. A raging fever sweeps through the
creature’s body. The creature has disadvantage on
Strength checks, Strength saving throws, and attack
rolls that use Strength.

Flesh Rot. The creature’s flesh decays. The creature
has disadvantage on Charisma checks and vulnerability
to all damage.

Mindfire. The creature’s mind becomes feverish. The
creature has disadvantage on Intelligence checks and
Intelligence saving throws, and the creature behaves as
if under the effects o f the confusion spell during combat.

Seizure. The creature is overcome with shaking.
The creature has disadvantage on Dexterity checks,
Dexterity saving throws, and attack rolls that
use Dexterity.

Slimy Doom. The creature begins to bleed
uncontrollably. The creature has disadvantage on
Constitution checks and Constitution saving throws.
In addition, whenever the creature takes damage, it is
stunned until the end o f its next turn.</Description>
    <ItemName>Contagion</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Contagion</SpellName>
    <School>Necromancy</School>
    <SpellLevel>5</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>100800</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Choose a spell o f 5th level or lower that you can cast, that
has a casting time o f 1 action, and that can target you.
You cast that spell—called the contingent spell—as part
of casting contingency, expending spell slots for both, but
the contingent spell doesn't come into effect. Instead, it
takes effect when a certain circumstance occurs. You
describe that circumstance when you cast the two spells.
For example, a contingency cast with water breathing
might stipulate that water breathing comes into effect
when you are engulfed in water or a similar liquid.
The contingent spell takes effect immediately after the
circumstance is met for the first time, whether or not you
want it to. and then contingency ends.

The contingent spell takes effect only on you, even
if it can normally target others. You can use only one
contingency spell at a time. If you cast this spell again,
the effect o f another contingency spell on you ends. Also,
contingency ends on you if its material component is
ever not on your person.</Description>
    <ItemName>Contingency</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Contingency</SpellName>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>6</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>144000</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>100</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a statuette of yourself carved from ivory and decorated with gems worth at least 1500gp.</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>1500</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>A flame, equivalent in brightness to a torch, springs
forth from an object that you touch. The effect looks like
a regular flame, but it creates no heat and doesn’t use
oxygen. A continual flame can be covered or hidden but
not smothered or quenched.</Description>
    <ItemName>Continual Flame</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Continual Flame</SpellName>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>2</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>true</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>ruby dust worth 50gp, which the spell consumes</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>50</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Until the spell ends, you control any freestanding water
inside an area you choose that is a cube up to 100 feet
on a side. You can choose from any o f the following
effects when you cast this spell. As an action on your
turn, you can repeat the same effect or choose a
different one.

Flood. You cause the water level o f all standing water in
the area to rise by as much as 20 feet. If the area includes
a shore, the flooding water spills over onto dry land.
If you choose an area in a large body o f water, you
instead create a 20-foot tall wave that travels from one
side o f the area to the other and then crashes down. Any
Huge or smaller vehicles in the wave’s path are carried
with it to the other side. Any Huge or smaller vehicles
struck by the wave have a 25 percent chance of capsizing.
The water level remains elevated until the spell ends
or you choose a different effect. If this effect produced
a wave, the wave repeats on the start o f your next turn
while the flood effect lasts.

Part Water. You cause water in the area to move
apart and create a trench. The trench extends across
the spell’s area, and the separated water forms a wall to
either side. The trench remains until the spell ends or
you choose a different effect. The water then slowly fills
in the trench over the course o f the next round until the
normal water level is restored.

Redirect Flow. You cause flowing water in the area
to move in a direction you choose, even if the water has
to flow over obstacles, up walls, or in other unlikely
directions. The water in the area moves as you direct
it, but once it moves beyond the spell’s area, it resumes
its flow based on the terrain conditions. The water
continues to move in the direction you chose until the
spell ends or you choose a different effect.

Whirlpool. This effect requires a body o f water
at least 50 feet square and 25 feet deep. You cause
a whirlpool to form in the center o f the area. The
whirlpool forms a vortex that is 5 feet w ide at the
base, up to 50 feet w ide at the top, and 25 feet tall. Any
creature or object in the water and within 25 feet o f the
vortex is pulled 10 feet toward it. A creature can swim
away from the vortex by m aking a Strength (Athletics)
check against your spell save DC.
When a creature enters the vortex for the first time on
a turn or starts its turn there, it must make a Strength
saving throw. On a failed save, the creature takes 2d8
bludgeoning damage and is caught in the vortex until
the spell ends. On a successful save, the creature takes
half damage, and isn’t caught in the vortex. A creature
caught in the vortex can use its action to try to swim
away from the vortex as described above, but has
disadvantage on the Strength (Athletics) check to do so.
The first time each turn that an object enters the
vortex, the object takes 2d8 bludgeoning damage; this
damage occurs each round it remains in the vortex.</Description>
    <ItemName>Control Water</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Control Water</SpellName>
    <School>Transmutation</School>
    <SpellLevel>4</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>300</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>100</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a drop of water and a pinch of dust</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You take control of the weather within 5 miles of  you
for the duration. You must be outdoors to cast this spell.
Moving to a place where you don’t have a clear path to
the sky ends the spell early.

When you cast the spell, you change the current
weather conditions, which are determined by the DM
based on the climate and season. You can change
precipitation, temperature, and wind. It takes 1d4 x 10
minutes for the new conditions to take effect. Once they
do so, you can change the conditions again. When the
spell ends, the weather gradually returns to normal.

When you change the weather conditions, find a
current condition on the following tables and change its
stage by one, up or down. When changing the wind, you
can change its direction.

Precipitation:

Stage Condition
1       Clear
2        Light clouds
3       Overcast or ground fog
4       Rain, hail, or snow
5       Torrential rain, driving hail, or blizzard

Temperature:
Stage      Condition
1             Unbearable heat
2             Hot
3             Warm
4             Cool
5             Cold
6             Arctic cold

Wind:

Stage Condition
1        Calm
2        Moderate wind
3        Strong wind
4        Gale
5         Storm</Description>
    <ItemName>Control Weather</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Control Weather</SpellName>
    <School>Transmutation</School>
    <SpellLevel>8</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>10000</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>4800</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>100</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>(burning incense and bits of earth and wood mixed in water</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You attempt to interrupt a creature in the process of
casting a spell. If the creature is casting a spell o f 3rd
level or lower, its spell fails and has no effect. If it is
casting a spell o f 4th level or higher, make an ability
check using your spellcasting ability. The DC equals 10
+ the spell’s level. On a success, the creature’s spell fails
and has no effect.</Description>
    <ItemName>Counterspell</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Counterspell</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a
spell slot o f 4th level or higher, the interrupted spell has
no effect if its level is less than or equal to the level o f the
spell slot you used.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Abjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>3</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_REACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>false</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You create 45 pounds o f food and 30 gallons of water
on the ground or in containers within range, enough
to sustain up to fifteen humanoids or five steeds for
24 hours. The food is bland but nourishing, and spoils
if uneaten after 24 hours. The water is clean and
doesn’t go bad.</Description>
    <ItemName>Create Food And Water</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Create Food And Water</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>3</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You either create or destroy water.

Create Water. You create up to 10 gallons o f clean
water within range in an open container. Alternatively,
the water falls as rain in a 30-foot cube within range,
extinguishing exposed flames in the area.

D estroy Water. You destroy up to 10 gallons o f water
in an open container within range. Alternatively, you
destroy fog in a 30-foot cube within range.</Description>
    <ItemName>Create Or Destroy Water</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Create Or Destroy Water</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level 
or higher, you create or destroy 10 additional gallons of water, 
or the size of the cube increases by 5 feet, for 
each slot level above 1st.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Transmutation</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a drop o f water if creating water or a few grains o f sand if destroying it</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You can cast this spell only at night. Choose up to three
corpses of Medium or Small humanoids within range.
Each corpse becomes a ghoul under your control. (The
DM has game statistics for these creatures.)

As a bonus action on each o f your turns, you can
mentally command any creature you animated with
this spell if the creature is within 120 feet o f you (if you
control multiple creatures, you can command any or all
o f them at the same time, issuing the same command to
each one). You decide what action the creature w ill take
and where it will move during its next turn, or you can
issue a general command, such as to guard a particular
chamber or corridor. If you issue no commands, the
creature only defends itself against hostile creatures.
Once given an order, the creature continues to follow it
until its task is complete.

The creature is under your control for 24 hours,
after which it stops obeying any command you have
given it. To maintain control o f the creature for another
24 hours, you must cast this spell on the creature
before the current 24-hour period ends. This use
of the spell reasserts your control over up to three
creatures you have animated with this spell, rather than
animating new ones.

</Description>
    <ItemName>Create Undead</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Create Undead</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a 7th-level spell slot, you 
can animate or reassert control over four ghouls. When you
cast this spell using an 8th-level spell slot, you can animate 
or reassert control over five ghouls or two ghasts or wights. 
When you cast this spell using a 9th-level spell slot, you can 
animate or reassert control over six ghouls, three ghasts or wights,
or two mummies.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Necromancy</School>
    <SpellLevel>6</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>10</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>10</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>one clay pot filled with grave dirt, one clay pot filled with brackish water, and one 150gp black onyx stone for each corpse</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>150</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You pull wisps of shadow material from the Shadowfell
to create a nonliving object of vegetable matter within
range: soft goods, rope, wood, or something similar. You
can also use this spell to create mineral objects such as
stone, crystal, or metal. The object created must be no
larger than a 5-foot cube, and the object must be o f a
form and material that you have seen before.
The duration depends on the object’s material. If
the object is composed o f multiple materials, use the
shortest duration.

Material                         Duration
Vegetable matter            1 day
Stone or crystal               12 hours
Precious metals               1 hour
Gems                              10 minutes
Adamantine or mithral   1 minute

Using any material created by this spell as another
spell’s material component causes that spell to fail.

When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 6th level or higher, 
the cube increases by 5 feet for each slot level above 5th.</Description>
    <ItemName>Creation</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Creation</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Illusion</School>
    <SpellLevel>5</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a tiny piece of matter of the same type of item you plan to create</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>One humanoid o f your choice that you can see within
range must succeed on a W isdom saving throw or
become charmed by you for the duration. While
the target is charmed in this way, a twisted crown
of jagged iron appears on its head, and a madness
glows in its eyes.

The charmed target must use its action before moving
on each of its turns to make a melee attack against a
creature other than itself that you mentally choose.

The target can act normally on its turn if you choose no
creature or if none are within its reach.
On your subsequent turns, you must use your action to
maintain control over the target, or the spell ends. Also,
the target can make a Wisdom saving throw at the end
of each o f its turns. On a success, the spell ends.</Description>
    <ItemName>Crown Of Madness</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Crown Of Madness</SpellName>
    <School>Enchantment</School>
    <SpellLevel>2</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>120</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Holy power radiates from you in an aura with a 30-foot
radius, awakening boldness in friendly creatures. Until
the spell ends, the aura moves with you, centered on
you. While in the aura, each nonhostile creature in the
aura (including you) deals an extra 1d4 radiant damage
when it hits with a w eapon attack.</Description>
    <ItemName>Crusader's Mantle</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Crusader's Mantle</SpellName>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>3</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>false</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>A creature you touch regains a number o f hit points
equal to 1d8 + your spellcasting ability modifier. This
spell has no effect on undead or constructs.</Description>
    <ItemName>Cure Wounds</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Cure Wounds</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a
spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the healing increases by
1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You create up to four torch-sized lights within range,
making them appear as torches, lanterns, or glowing
orbs that hover in the air for the duration. You can
also combine the four lights into one glowing vaguely
humanoid form of Medium size. Whichever form you
choose, each light sheds dim light in a 10-foot radius.
As a bonus action on your turn, you can move the
lights up to 60 feet to a new spot within range. A light
must be within 20 feet of another light created by this
spell, and a light winks out if it exceeds the spell’s range.</Description>
    <ItemName>Dancing Lights</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Dancing Lights</SpellName>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>120</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_NONE</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Magical darkness spreads from a point you choose
within range to fill a 15-foot-radius sphere for the
duration. The darkness spreads around corners.
A creature with darkvision can’t see through this
darkness, and nonmagical light can’t illuminate it.
If the point you choose is on an object you are holding
or one that isn’t being w orn or carried, the darkness
emanates from the object and moves with it. Completely
covering the source o f the darkness with an opaque
object, such as a bowl or a helm, blocks the darkness.
If any of this spell’s area overlaps with an area o f light
created by a spell o f 2nd level or lower, the spell that
created the light is dispelled.</Description>
    <ItemName>Darkness</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Darkness</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>2</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>100</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>15</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_SPHERE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>false</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>bat fur and a drop of pitch or piece of coal</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You touch a willing creature to grant it the ability to
see in the dark. For the duration, that creature has
darkvision out to a range of 60 feet.</Description>
    <ItemName>Darkvision</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Darkvision</SpellName>
    <School>Transmutation</School>
    <SpellLevel>2</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>4800</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>either a pinch of dried carrot or an agate</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>A 60-foot-radius sphere o f light spreads out from a point
you choose within range. The sphere is bright light and
sheds dim light for an additional 60 feet.

If you chose a point on an object you are holding or
one that isn’t being worn or carried, the light shines
from the object and moves with it. Completely covering
the affected object with an opaque object, such as a bowl
or a helm, blocks the light.

If any of this spell’s area overlaps with an area of
darkness created by a spell o f 3rd level or lower, the
spell that created the darkness is dispelled.</Description>
    <ItemName>Daylight</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Daylight</SpellName>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>3</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>For the duration, you sense the presence of magic
within 30 feet of you. If you sense magic in this way, you
can use your action to see a faint aura around any visible
creature or object in the area that bears magic, and you
learn its school of magic, if any.

The spell can penetrate most barriers, but it is blocked
by 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of common metal, a thin sheet
of lead, or 3 feet of wood or dirt.</Description>
    <ItemName>Detect Magic</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Detect Magic</SpellName>
    <School>Divination</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>100</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>true</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You make yourself—including your clothing, armor,
weapons, and other belongings on your person—look
different until the spell ends or until you use your action
to dismiss it. You can seem 1 foot shorter or taller and
can appear thin, fat, or in between. You can’t change
your body type, so you must adopt a form that has the
sam e basic arrangement of limbs. Otherwise, the extent
of the illusion is up to you.

The changes wrought by this spell fail to hold up to
physical inspection. For example, if you use this spell
to add a hat to your outfit, objects pass through the hat,
and anyone who touches it would feel nothing or would
feel your head and hair. If you use this spell to appear
thinner than you are, the hand of someone who reaches
out to touch you would bump into you while it was
seem ingly still in midair.

To discern that you are disguised, a creature can use
its action to inspect your appearance and must succeed
on an Intelligence (Investigation) check against your
spell save DC.</Description>
    <ItemName>Disguise Self</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Disguise Self</SpellName>
    <School>Illusion</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>This spell allows you to move at an incredible pace.
When you cast this spell, and then as a bonus action
on each of your turns until the spell ends, you can take
the Dash action.</Description>
    <ItemName>Expeditious Retreat</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Expeditious Retreat</SpellName>
    <School>Transmutation</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>100</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_BONUS_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Bolstering yourself with a necromantic facsimile of life,
you gain 1d4 + 4 temporary hit points for the duration..</Description>
    <ItemName>False Life</ItemName>
    <SpellName>False Life</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a
spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you gain 5 additional
temporary hit points for each slot level above 1st.
		</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Necromancy</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a small amount of alcohol or distilled spirits</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Choose up to five falling creatures within range. 
A falling creature's rate of descent slows to 60 feet per
round until the spell ends. If the creature lands before
the spell ends, it takes no falling damage and can land
on its feet, and the spell ends for that creature.</Description>
    <ItemName>Feather Fall</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Feather Fall</SpellName>
    <School>Transmutation</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_REACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>false</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a small feather or piece of down</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You gain the service of a familiar, a spirit that takes an animal form you choose: bat, cat, crab, frog (toad), 
hawk,lizard, octopus, owl, poisonous snake, fish (quipper),rat, raven, sea horse, spider, or weasel. 
Appearing in an unoccupied space within range, the familiar has the statistics of the chosen form, though 
it is a celestial, fey, or fiend (your choice) instead of a beast. Your familiar acts independently of you, 
but it always obeys your commands. In combat, it rolls its own initiative and acts on its own turn. 
A familiar can’t attack, but it can take other actions as normal. When the familiar drops to 0 hit points, 
it disappears, leaving behind no physical form. It reappears after you cast this spell again

While your familiar is within 100 feet of you, you can communicate with it telepathically. Additionally,
as an action, you can see through your familiar’s eyes and hear what it hears until the start of your next turn,
gaining the benefits of any special senses that the familiar has. During this time, you are deaf and blind
with regard to your own senses. As an action, you can temporarily dismiss your familiar. It disappears 
into a pocket dimension where it awaits your summons. Alternatively, you can dismiss it forever. 

As an action while it is temporarily dismissed, you can cause it to reappear in any unoccupied space
within 30 feet of you. You can’t have more than one familiar at a time. If you cast this spell while you 
already have a familiar, you instead cause it to adopt a new form. Choose one of the forms from the above list. 
Your familiar transforms into the chosen creature.

Finally, when you cast a spell with a range of touch, your familiar can deliver the spell as if it had cast the
spell. Your familiar must be within 100 feet of you, and it must use its reaction to deliver the spell when you cast
it. If the spell requires an attack roll, you use your attack modifier for the roll.</Description>
    <ItemName>Find Familiar</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Find Familiar</SpellName>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>10</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>600</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>10 gp worth of charcoal,incense, and herbs that must be consumed by fire in a brass brazier</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You hurl a mote of fire at a creature or object within
range. Make a ranged spell attack against the
target. On a hit, the target takes 1d10 fire damage. A
flammable object hit by this spell ignites if it isn't being
worn or carried. This spell’s damage increases by 1d10 when you reach
5th level (2d10), 11th level (3d10), and 17th level (4d10).</Description>
    <ItemName>Fire Bolt</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Fire Bolt</SpellName>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>120</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You create a 20-foot-radius sphere of fog centered on a
point within range. The sphere spreads around corners,
and its area is heavily obscured. It lasts for the duration
or until a wind of moderate or greater speed (at least 10
miles per hour) disperses it</Description>
    <ItemName>Fog Cloud</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Fog Cloud</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a
spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the radius of the fog
increases by 20 feet for each slot level above 1st.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>120</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>20</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_SPHERE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>For the duration, you have advantage on all Charisma
checks directed at one creature of your choice that isn’t
hostile toward you. When the spell ends, the creature
realizes that you used magic to influence its mood
and becomes hostile toward you. A creature prone
to violence might attack you. Another creature might
seek retribution in other ways (at the DM’s discretion),
depending on the nature o f your interaction with it.</Description>
    <ItemName>Friends</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Friends</SpellName>
    <School>Enchantment</School>
    <SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_NONE</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>false</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Slick grease covers the ground in a 10-foot square
centered on a point within range and turns it into
difficult terrain for the duration.
When the grease appears, each creature standing in
its area must succeed on a Dexterity saving throw or fall
prone. A creature that enters the area or ends its turn
there must also succeed on a Dexterity saving throw
or fall prone.</Description>
    <ItemName>Grease</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Grease</SpellName>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>10</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_SQUARE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a bit of pork rind or butter</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You choose one object that you must touch throughout
the casting of the spell. If it is a magic item or som e
other magic-imbued object, you learn its properties
and how to use them, whether it requires attunement
to use, and how many charges it has, if any. You learn
whether any spells are affecting the item and what they
are. If the item was created by a spell, you learn which
spell created it.

If you instead touch a creature throughout the casting,
you learn what spells, if any, are currently affecting it.</Description>
    <ItemName>Identify</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Identify</SpellName>
    <School>Divination</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>10</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a pearl worth at least 100 gp and an owl feather</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You write on parchment, paper, or some other suitable
writing material and imbue it with a potent illusion that
lasts for the duration.

To you and any creatures you designate when you
cast the spell, the writing appears normal, written in
your hand, and conveys whatever meaning you intended
when you wrote the text. To all others, the writing
appears as if it were written in an unknown or magical
script that is unintelligible. Alternatively, you can cause
the writing to appear to be an entirely different message,
written in a different hand and language, though the
language must be one you know. 

Should the spell be dispelled, the original script and
the illusion both disappear.

A creature with truesight can read the hidden message.</Description>
    <ItemName>Illusory Script</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Illusory Script</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Illusion</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>144000</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>10</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>false</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a lead-based ink worth at least 10gp, which the spell consumes</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You touch a creature. The creature’s jump distance is
tripled until the spell ends.</Description>
    <ItemName>Jump</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Jump</SpellName>
    <School>Transmutation</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a grasshopper’s hind leg</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You touch one object that is no larger than 10 feet in any
dimension. Until the spell ends, the object sheds bright
light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional
20 feet. The light can be colored as you like. Completely
covering the object with something opaque blocks the
light. The spell ends if you cast it again or dismiss it
as an action. If you target an object held or worn by a hostile
creature, that creature must succeed on a Dexterity
saving throw to avoid the spell.</Description>
    <ItemName>Light</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Light</SpellName>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>100</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>false</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You touch a creature. The target’s speed increases by 10
feet until the spell ends.</Description>
    <ItemName>Longstrider</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Longstrider</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using
a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one
additional creature for each slot level above 1st.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Transmutation</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a pinch of dirt</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You touch a willing creature who isn’t wearing armor,
and a protective magical force surrounds it until the
spell ends. The target’s base AC becom es 13 + its
Dexterity modifier. The spell ends if the target dons
armor or if you dismiss the spell as an action.</Description>
    <ItemName>Mage Armor</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Mage Armor</SpellName>
    <School>Abjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>4800</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a piece of cured leather</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>A spectral, floating hand appears at a point you choose
within range. The hand lasts for the duration or until
you dismiss it as an action. The hand vanishes if it is
ever more than 30 feet away from you or if you cast
this spell again. You can use your action to control the hand. You can
use the hand to manipulate an object, open an unlocked
door or container, stow or retrieve an item from an open
container, or pour the contents out o f a vial. You can
move the hand up to 30 feet each time you use it.
The hand can’t attack, activate magic items, or carry
more than 10 pounds.</Description>
    <ItemName>Mage Hand</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Mage Hand</SpellName>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_NONE</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You create three glowing darts of magical force. Each
dart hits a creature of your choice that you can see
within range. A dart deals 1d4 + 1 force damage to its
target. The darts all strike simultaneously, and you can
direct them to hit one creature or several.</Description>
    <ItemName>Magic Missile</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Magic Missile</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a
spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the spell creates one
more dart for each slot level above 1st.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>120</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>This spell repairs a single break or tear in an object
you touch, such as a broken chain link, two halves of
a broken key, a torn cloak, or a leaking wineskin. As
long as the break or tear is no larger than 1 foot in
any dimension, you mend it. leaving no trace of the
former damage. This spell can physically repair a magic item
or construct, but the spell can’t restore magic to
such an object.</Description>
    <ItemName>Mending</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Mending</SpellName>
    <School>Transmutation</School>
    <SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>10</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You point your finger toward a creature within range
and whisper a message. The target (and only the target)
hears the message and can reply in a whisper that only
you can hear.
You can cast this spell through solid objects if you
are familiar with the target and know it is beyond
the barrier. Magical silence. 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of
common metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of wood
blocks the spell. The spell doesn’t have to follow a
straight line and can travel freely around corners or
through openings.</Description>
    <ItemName>Message</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Message</SpellName>
    <School>Transmutation</School>
    <SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>120</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You create a sound or an image of an object within
range that lasts for the duration. The illusion also ends if
you dismiss it as an action or cast this spell again.
If you create a sound, its volume can range from a
whisper to a scream . It can be your voice, someone
else’s voice, a lion’s roar, a beating of drums, or any
other sound you choose. The sound continues unabated
throughout the duration, or you can make discrete
sounds at different times before the spell ends.
If you create an image of an object—such as a chair,
muddy footprints, or a small chest—it must be no larger
than a 5-foot cube. The image can’t create sound, light,
smell, or any other sensory effect. Physical interaction
with the image reveals it to be an illusion, because
things can pass through it.
If a creature uses its action to examine the sound or
image, the creature can determine that it is an illusion
with a successful Intelligence (Investigation) check
against your spell save DC. If a creature discerns the
illusion for what it is, the illusion becomes faint to
the creature
		</Description>
    <ItemName>Minor Illusion</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Minor Illusion</SpellName>
    <School>Illusion</School>
    <SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_NONE</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>false</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You extend your hand toward a creature you can see
within range and project a puff of noxious gas from your
palm. The creature must succeed on a Constitution
saving throw or take 1d12 poison damage.
This spell’s damage increases by 1d12 when you reach
5th level (2d12), 11th level (3d12), and 17th level (4d12).
		</Description>
    <ItemName>Poison Spray</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Poison Spray</SpellName>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>10</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_NONE</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>This spell is a minor magical trick that novice
spellcasters use for practice. You create one of the
following magical effects within range:
• You create an instantaneous, harm less sensory effect,
such as a shower of sparks, a puff of wind, faint musical notes, or an odd odor.

• You instantaneously light or snuff out a candle, a
torch, or a small campfire.

• You instantaneously clean or soil an object no larger
than 1 cubic foot.

• You chill, warm, or flavor up to 1 cubic foot of nonliving material for 1 hour.

• You make a color, a small mark, or a sym bol appear
on an object or a surface for 1 hour.

• You create a nonmagical trinket or an illusory im age
that can fit in your hand and that lasts until the end of
your next turn.

If you cast this spell multiple times, you can have up to
three of its non-instantaneous effects active at a time,
and you can dismiss such an effect as an action
		</Description>
    <ItemName>Presdigitation</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Presdigitation</SpellName>
    <School>Transmutation</School>
    <SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>10</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_NONE</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Until the spell ends, one willing creature you
touch is protected against certain types of
creatures: aberrations, celestials, elementals, fey,
fiends, and undead.

The protection grants several benefits. Creatures of
those types have disadvantage on attack rolls against
the target. The target also can’t be charmed, frightened,
or possessed by them. If the target is already charmed,
frightened, or possessed by such a creature, the target
has advantage on any new saving throw against the
relevant effect.</Description>
    <ItemName>Protection from Evil and Good</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Protection from Evil and Good</SpellName>
    <School>Abjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>100</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>holy water or powdered silver and iron, which the spell consumes</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>A frigid beam of blue-white light streaks toward a
creature within range. Make a ranged spell attack
against the target. On a hit, it takes 1d8 cold damage,
and its speed is reduced by 10 feet until the start of
your next turn.
The spell’s damage increases by 1d8 when you reach
5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).
		</Description>
    <ItemName>Ray of Frost</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Ray of Frost</SpellName>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_NONE</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>A ray of sickening greenish energy lashes out toward
a creature within range. Make a ranged spell attack
against the target. On a hit, the target takes 2d8 poison
damage and must make a Constitution saving throw.
On a failed save, it is also poisoned until the end of
your next turn.</Description>
    <ItemName>Ray of Sickness</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Ray of Sickness</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a
spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by
1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Necromancy</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>An invisible barrier of magical force appears and
protects you. Until the start of your next turn, you have a
+5 bonus to AC, including against the triggering attack,
and you take no damage from magic missile.
</Description>
    <ItemName>Shield</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Shield</SpellName>
    <School>Abjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_REACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>Lightning springs from your hand to deliver a shock to
a creature you try to touch. Make a melee spell attack
against the target. You have advantage on the attack roll
if the target is wearing arm or made of metal. On a hit,
the target takes 1d8 lightning damage, and it can’t take
reactions until the start of its next turn.
The spell’s damage increases by 1d8 when you reach
5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).
		</Description>
    <ItemName>Shocking Grasp</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Shocking Grasp</SpellName>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You create the image of an object, a creature, or some
other visible phenomenon that is no larger than a 15-foot
cube. The image appears at a spot within range and
lasts for the duration. 

The image is purely visual; it isn't accompanied by sound,
smell, or other sensory effects. You can use your action to 
cause the image to m ove to any spot within range. As the 
image changes location, you can alter its appearance so that 
its movements appear natural for the image. For example, if 
you create an image of a creature and move it, you can alter the
image so that it appears to be walking.

Physical interaction with the image reveals it to be an
illusion, because things can pass through it. A creature
that uses its action to examine the image can determine
that it is an illusion with a successful Intelligence
(Investigation) check against your spell save DC. If a
creature discerns the illusion for what it is, the creature
can see through the image.</Description>
    <ItemName>Silent Image</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Silent Image</SpellName>
    <School>Illusion</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>100</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a bit of fleece</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>This spell sends creatures into a magical slumber.
Roll 5d8; the total is how many hit points of creatures
this spell can affect. Creatures within 20 feet of
a point you choose within range are affected in
ascending order of their current hit points (ignoring
unconscious creatures).

Starting with the creature that has the lowest current
hit points, each creature affected by this spell falls
unconscious until the spell ends, the sleeper takes
damage, or someone uses an action to shake or slap the
sleeper awake. Subtract each creature’s hit points from
the total before moving on to the creature with the next
lowest hit points. A creature’s hit points must be equal
to or less than the remaining total for that creature
to be affected.

Undead and creatures immune to being charmed
aren’t affected by this spell.</Description>
    <ItemName>Sleep</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Sleep</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a
spell slot of 2nd level or higher, roll an additional 2d8 for
each slot level above 1st.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Enchantment</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>90</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a pinch of fine sand, rose petals, or a cricket</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>A creature of your choice that you can see within range
perceives everything as hilariously funny and falls
into fits of laughter if this spell affects it. The target
must succeed on a Wisdom saving throw or fall prone,
becoming incapacitated and unable to stand up for the
duration. A creature with an Intelligence score of 4 or
less isn’t affected.

At the end of each of its turns, and each time it takes
damage, the target can make another Wisdom saving
throw. The target has advantage on the saving throw if
it’s triggered by damage. On a success, the spell ends.</Description>
    <ItemName>Tasha’s Hideous Laughter</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Tasha’s Hideous Laughter</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels />
    <School>Enchantment</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>tiny tarts and a feather that is waved in the air</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>This spell creates a circular, horizontal plane of force,
3 feet in diameter and 1 inch thick, that floats 3 feet
above the ground in an unoccupied space of your choice
that you can see within range. The disk remains for the
duration, and can hold up to 500 pounds. If more weight
is placed on it, the spell ends, and everything on the disk
falls to the ground.
The disk is immobile while you are within 20 feet of
it. If you move more than 20 feet away from it, the disk
follows you so that it remains within 20 feet of you. It
can move across uneven terrain, up or down stairs,
slopes and the like, but it can’t cross an elevation change
o f 10 feet or more. For example, the disk can’t move
across a 10-foot-deep pit, nor could it leave such a pit if it
was created at the bottom.
If you move m ore than 100 feet from the disk (typically
because it can’t move around an obstacle to follow you),
the spell ends.</Description>
    <ItemName>Tenser’s Floating Disk</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Tenser’s Floating Disk</SpellName>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>true</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a drop of mercury</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>A wave of thunderous force sweeps out from you. Each
creature in a 15-foot cube originating from you must
make a Constitution saving throw. On a failed save, a
creature takes 2d8 thunder damage and is pushed 10
feet away from you. On a successful save, the creature
takes half as much damage and isn’t pushed.
In addition, unsecured objects that are completely
within the area of effect are automatically pushed 10 feet
away from you by the spell’s effect, and the spell emits a
thunderous boom audible out to 300 feet.</Description>
    <ItemName>Thunderwave</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Thunderwave</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a
spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by
1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>15</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_CUBE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>You extend your hand and point a finger at a target in
range. Your magic grants you a brief insight into the target’s defenses. 
On your next turn, you gain advantage on your first attack roll against the target, provided that
this spell hasn’t ended.
		</Description>
    <ItemName>True Strike</ItemName>
    <SpellName>True Strike</SpellName>
    <School>Divination</School>
    <SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_NONE</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent />
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>This spell creates an invisible, mindless, shapeless
force that perform s simple tasks at your command until
the spell ends. The servant springs into existence in an
unoccupied space on the ground within range. It has AC
10, 1 hit point, and a Strength of 2, and it can’t attack. 

If it drops to 0 hit points, the spell ends.
Once on each of your turns as a bonus action, you can
mentally command the servant to move up to 15 feet and
interact with an object. The servant can perform simple
tasks that a human servant could do, such as fetching
things, cleaning, mending, folding clothes, lighting
fires, serving food, and pouring wine. Once you give the
command, the servant perform s the task to the best of
its ability until it completes the task, then waits for your
next command.
If you command the servant to perform a task that
would move it more than 60 feet away from you,
the spell ends.</Description>
    <ItemName>Unseen Servant</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Unseen Servant</SpellName>
    <School>Conjuration</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>true</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a piece of string and a bit of wood</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
  <PlayerSpell>
    <Description>A beam of crackling, blue energy lances out toward
a creature within range, forming a sustained arc of
lightning between you and the target. Make a ranged
spell attack against that creature. On a hit, the target
takes 1d12 lightning damage, and on each of your turns
for the duration, you can use your action to deal 1d12
lightning damage to the target automatically. The spell
ends if you use your action to do anything else. The spell
also ends if the target is ever outside the spell’s range or
if it has total cover from you.</Description>
    <ItemName>Witch Bolt</ItemName>
    <SpellName>Witch Bolt</SpellName>
    <AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using
a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the initial damage
increases by 1d12 for each slot level above 1st.</AtHigherLevels>
    <School>Evocation</School>
    <SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
    <SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
    <SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
    <IsUntilDispelled>false</IsUntilDispelled>
    <AoeSize>0</AoeSize>
    <AoeType>AOE_TYPE_NONE</AoeType>
    <RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
    <CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
    <CastingTimePeriod>0</CastingTimePeriod>
    <IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
    <IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
    <IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
    <IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
    <IsRitual>false</IsRitual>
    <MaterialComponent>a twig from a tree that has been struck by lightning</MaterialComponent>
    <MaterialCost>0</MaterialCost>
  </PlayerSpell>
</ArrayOfPlayerSpell>