<ArrayOfPlayerSpell xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	
	<!-- Cantrips -->
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Acid Splash</SpellName>
		<School>Conjuration</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
		
		<Description>You hurl a bubble of acid. Choose one creature within
range, or choose two creatures within range that are
within 5 feet of each other. A target must succeed on a
Dexterity saving throw or take 1d6 acid damage.
This spell’s damage increases by 1d6 when you reach
5th level (2d6), 11th level (3d6), and 17th level (4d6).</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Blade Ward</SpellName>
		<School>Abjuration</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
		<RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
		
		<Description>You extend your hand and trace a sigil of warding in the
air. Until the end of your next turn, you have resistance
against bludgeoning, piercing, and slashing damage
dealt by weapon attacks.</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Chill Touch</SpellName>
		<School>Necromancy</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>120</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
		
		<Description>You create a ghostly, skeletal hand in the space of a
creature within range. Make a ranged spell attack
against the creature to assail it with the chill of the
grave. On a hit, the target takes 1d8 necrotic damage,
and it can’t regain hit points until the start of your next
turn. Until then, the hand clings to the target.
If you hit an undead target, it also has disadvantage on
attack rolls against you until the end of your next turn.
This spell’s damage increases by 1d8 when you reach
5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Dancing Lights</SpellName>
		<School>Evocation</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>120</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
		
		<Description>You create up to four torch-sized lights within range,
making them appear as torches, lanterns, or glowing
orbs that hover in the air for the duration. You can
also combine the four lights into one glowing vaguely
humanoid form of Medium size. Whichever form you
choose, each light sheds dim light in a 10-foot radius.
As a bonus action on your turn, you can move the
lights up to 60 feet to a new spot within range. A light
must be within 20 feet of another light created by this
spell, and a light winks out if it exceeds the spell’s range.</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Fire Bolt</SpellName>
		<School>Evocation</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>120</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
		
		<Description>You hurl a mote of fire at a creature or object within
range. Make a ranged spell attack against the
target. On a hit, the target takes 1d10 fire damage. A
flammable object hit by this spell ignites if it isn't being
worn or carried. This spell’s damage increases by 1d10 when you reach
5th level (2d10), 11th level (3d10), and 17th level (4d10).</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Friends</SpellName>
		<School>Enchantment</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>false</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
		
		<Description>For the duration, you have advantage on all Charisma
checks directed at one creature of your choice that isn’t
hostile toward you. When the spell ends, the creature
realizes that you used magic to influence its mood
and becomes hostile toward you. A creature prone
to violence might attack you. Another creature might
seek retribution in other ways (at the DM’s discretion),
depending on the nature o f your interaction with it.</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Light</SpellName>
		<School>Evocation</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
		<RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>false</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>100</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
		
		<Description>You touch one object that is no larger than 10 feet in any
dimension. Until the spell ends, the object sheds bright
light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional
20 feet. The light can be colored as you like. Completely
covering the object with something opaque blocks the
light. The spell ends if you cast it again or dismiss it
as an action. If you target an object held or worn by a hostile
creature, that creature must succeed on a Dexterity
saving throw to avoid the spell.</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Mage Hand</SpellName>
		<School>Conjuration</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
		
		<Description>A spectral, floating hand appears at a point you choose
within range. The hand lasts for the duration or until
you dismiss it as an action. The hand vanishes if it is
ever more than 30 feet away from you or if you cast
this spell again. You can use your action to control the hand. You can
use the hand to manipulate an object, open an unlocked
door or container, stow or retrieve an item from an open
container, or pour the contents out o f a vial. You can
move the hand up to 30 feet each time you use it.
The hand can’t attack, activate magic items, or carry
more than 10 pounds.</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Mending</SpellName>
		<School>Transmutation</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
		<CastingTimePeriod>10</CastingTimePeriod>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
		<RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
		
		<Description>This spell repairs a single break or tear in an object
you touch, such as a broken chain link, two halves of
a broken key, a torn cloak, or a leaking wineskin. As
long as the break or tear is no larger than 1 foot in
any dimension, you mend it. leaving no trace of the
former damage. This spell can physically repair a magic item
or construct, but the spell can’t restore magic to
such an object.</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Message</SpellName>
		<School>Transmutation</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>120</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
		<Description>You point your finger toward a creature within range
and whisper a message. The target (and only the target)
hears the message and can reply in a whisper that only
you can hear.
You can cast this spell through solid objects if you
are familiar with the target and know it is beyond
the barrier. Magical silence. 1 foot of stone, 1 inch of
com m on metal, a thin sheet of lead, or 3 feet of w ood
blocks the spell. The spell doesn’t have to follow a
straight line and can travel freely around corners or
through openings.</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Minor Illusion</SpellName>
		<School>Illusion</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>false</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
		<Description>You create a sound or an image of an object within
range that lasts for the duration. The illusion also ends if
you dismiss it as an action or cast this spell again.
If you create a sound, its volume can range from a
whisper to a scream . It can be your voice, someone
else’s voice, a lion’s roar, a beating of drums, or any
other sound you choose. The sound continues unabated
throughout the duration, or you can make discrete
sounds at different times before the spell ends.
If you create an image of an object—such as a chair,
muddy footprints, or a small chest—it must be no larger
than a 5-foot cube. The image can’t create sound, light,
smell, or any other sensory effect. Physical interaction
with the image reveals it to be an illusion, because
things can pass through it.
If a creature uses its action to examine the sound or
image, the creature can determine that it is an illusion
with a successful Intelligence (Investigation) check
against your spell save DC. If a creature discerns the
illusion for what it is, the illusion becomes faint to
the creature
		</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Poison Spray</SpellName>
		<School>Conjuration</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>10</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
		<Description>You extend your hand toward a creature you can see
within range and project a puff of noxious gas from your
palm. The creature must succeed on a Constitution
saving throw or take 1d12 poison damage.
This spell’s damage increases by 1d12 when you reach
5th level (2d12), 11th level (3d12), and 17th level (4d12).
		</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Presdigitation</SpellName>
		<School>Transmutation</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>10</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
		<Description>This spell is a minor magical trick that novice
spellcasters use for practice. You create one of the
following magical effects within range:
• You create an instantaneous, harm less sensory effect,
such as a shower of sparks, a puff of wind, faint musical notes, or an odd odor.

• You instantaneously light or snuff out a candle, a
torch, or a small campfire.

• You instantaneously clean or soil an object no larger
than 1 cubic foot.

• You chill, warm, or flavor up to 1 cubic foot of nonliving material for 1 hour.

• You make a color, a small mark, or a sym bol appear
on an object or a surface for 1 hour.

• You create a nonmagical trinket or an illusory im age
that can fit in your hand and that lasts until the end of
your next turn.

If you cast this spell multiple times, you can have up to
three of its non-instantaneous effects active at a time,
and you can dismiss such an effect as an action
		</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Ray of Frost</SpellName>
		<School>Evocation</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
		<Description>A frigid beam of blue-white light streaks toward a
creature within range. Make a ranged spell attack
against the target. On a hit, it takes 1d8 cold damage,
and its speed is reduced by 10 feet until the start of
your next turn.
The spell’s damage increases by 1d8 when you reach
5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).
		</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Shocking Grasp</SpellName>
		<School>Evocation</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
		<RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_TOUCH</RangeType>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
		<Description>Lightning springs from your hand to deliver a shock to
a creature you try to touch. Make a melee spell attack
against the target. You have advantage on the attack roll
if the target is wearing arm or made of metal. On a hit,
the target takes 1d8 lightning damage, and it can’t take
reactions until the start of its next turn.
The spell’s damage increases by 1d8 when you reach
5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).
		</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>True Strike</SpellName>
		<School>Divination</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
		<Description>You extend your hand and point a finger at a target in
range. Your magic grants you a brief insight into the target’s defenses. 
On your next turn, you gain advantage on your first attack roll against the target, provided that
this spell hasn’t ended.
		</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<!-- Level 1 Spells -->
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Alarm</SpellName>
		<School>Abjuration</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
		<CastingTimePeriod>10</CastingTimePeriod>
		<SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>4800</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
		<Description>You set an alarm against unwanted intrusion. Choose
a door, a window, or an area within range that is no
larger than a 20-foot cube. Until the spell ends, an alarm
alerts you whenever a Tiny or larger creature touches
or enters the warded area. When you cast the spell, you
can designate creatures that won’t set off the alarm. You
also choose whether the alarm is mental or audible.
A mental alarm alerts you with a ping in your mind
if you are within 1 mile of the warded area. This ping
awakens you if you are sleeping. An audible alarm produces 
the sound of a hand bell for 10 seconds within 60 feet.</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>

	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Burning Hands</SpellName>
		<School>Evocation</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
		<RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_SELF</RangeType>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
		<AoeSize>15</AoeSize>
		<AoeType>AOE_TYPE_CONE</AoeType>
		<IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
		<Description>As you hold your hands with thumbs touching and fingers spread, 
a thin sheet of flames shoots forth from your outstretched fingertips. 
Each creature in a 15-foot cone must make a Dexterity saving throw. 
A creature takes 3d6 fire damage on a failed save, or half as much
damage on a successful one. The fire ignites any flammable objects in 
the area that aren’t being worn or carried.</Description>
		<AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, 
the damage increases by 1d6 for each slot level above 1st.</AtHigherLevels>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Charm Person</SpellName>
		<School>Enchantment</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
		<RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>600</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
		<Description>You attempt to charm a humanoid you can see within
range. It must make a Wisdom saving throw, and does
so with advantage if you or your companions are fighting
it. If it fails the saving throw, it is charmed by you until
the spell ends or until you or your companions do
anything harmful to it. The charmed creature regards
you as a friendly acquaintance. When the spell ends, the
creature knows it was charmed by you.</Description>
		<AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using
a spell slot of 2nd level or higher, you can target one
additional creature for each slot level above 1st. The
creatures must be within 30 feet of each other when
you target them.</AtHigherLevels>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Chromatic Orb</SpellName>
		<School>Evocation</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellRange>90</SpellRange>
		<RangeType>RANGE_TYPE_RANGED</RangeType>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
		<MaterialComponent>a diamond worth at least 50 gp</MaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
		<Description>You hurl a 4-inch-diameter sphere of energy at a
creature that you can see within range. You choose
acid, cold, fire, lightning, poison, or thunder for the type
of orb you create, and then make a ranged spell attack
against the target. If the attack hits, the creature takes
3d8 damage of the type you chose.</Description>
		<AtHigherLevels>When you cast this spell using a
spell slot of 2nd level or higher, the damage increases by
1d8 for each slot level above 1st.</AtHigherLevels>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Color Spray</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Comprehend Languages</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Detect Magic</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Disguise Self</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Expeditious Retreat</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>

	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>False Life</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Feather Fall</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Find Familiar</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>

	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Fog Cloud</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Grease</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Identify</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Illusory Script</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Jump</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Longstrider</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Mage Armor</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Magic Missile</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Protection from Evil and Good</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Ray of Sickness</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Shield</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Silent Image</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Sleep</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Tasha’s Hideous Laughter</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Tenser’s Floating Disk</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Thunderwave</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Unseen Servant</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Witch Bolt</SpellName>
		<SpellLevel>1</SpellLevel>
	</PlayerSpell>	
</ArrayOfPlayerSpell>