<ArrayOfPlayerAbility xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	
	<PlayerAbility>
		<AttributeName>Darkvision</AttributeName>
		<Description>You can see in dim light within 60 feet as if it were bright light and in darkness as if it were dim light. You can't discern color in darkness, only shades of gray.</Description>
		<MaximumCharges>0</MaximumCharges>
	</PlayerAbility>
	
	<PlayerAbility>
		<AttributeName>Dwarven Resilience</AttributeName>
		<Description>You have advantage on saving throws against poison, and you have resistance against poison damage.</Description>
		<MaximumCharges>0</MaximumCharges>
	</PlayerAbility>
	
	<PlayerAbility>
		<AttributeName>Dwarven Toughness</AttributeName>
		<Description>Your hit point maximum increased by 1, and it increases by 1 every time you gain a level.</Description>
		<MaximumCharges>0</MaximumCharges>
	</PlayerAbility>
	
	<PlayerAbility>
		<AttributeName>Stonecunning</AttributeName>
		<Description> Whenever you make an Intelligence (History) check related to the origin of stonework, you are considered proficient in the History skill and add double your proficiency bonus to the check, instead of your normal proficiency bonus.</Description>
		<MaximumCharges>0</MaximumCharges>
	</PlayerAbility>
	
	<PlayerAbility>
		<AttributeName>Fey Ancestry</AttributeName>
		<Description>You have advantage on saving throws against being charmed, and magic can’t put you to sleep.</Description>
		<MaximumCharges>0</MaximumCharges>
	</PlayerAbility>
	
	<PlayerAbility>
		<AttributeName>Trance</AttributeName>
		<Description> Elves don’t need to sleep. Instead, they meditate deeply, remaining semiconscious, for 4 hours a day. (The Common word for such meditation is “trance.”) While meditating, you can dream after a fashion; such dreams are actually mental exercises that have becom e reflexive through years of practice. After resting in this way, you gain the same benefit that a human does from 8 hours of sleep. </Description>
		<MaximumCharges>0</MaximumCharges>
	</PlayerAbility>

<!-- Fighter class abilities -->
	<PlayerAbility>
		<AttributeName>Archery Fighting Style</AttributeName>
		<Description>You gain a +2 bonus to attack rolls you make with ranged weapons.</Description>
		<MaximumCharges>0</MaximumCharges>
	</PlayerAbility>
	
	<PlayerAbility>
		<AttributeName>Defense Fighting Style</AttributeName>
		<Description>While you are wearing armor, you gain a +1 bonus to AC.</Description>
		<MaximumCharges>0</MaximumCharges>
	</PlayerAbility>
	
	<PlayerAbility>
		<AttributeName>Dueling Fighting Style</AttributeName>
		<Description>When you are wielding a melee weapon in one hand and no other weapons, you gain a +2 bonus to damage rolls with that weapon.</Description>
		<MaximumCharges>0</MaximumCharges>
	</PlayerAbility>
	
	<PlayerAbility>
		<AttributeName>Great Weapon Fighting Style</AttributeName>
		<Description>When you roll a 1 or 2 on a damage die for an attack you make with a melee weapon that you are wielding with two hands, you can reroll the die and must use the new roll, even if the new roll is a 1 or a 2. The weapon must have the two-handed or versatile property for you to gain this benefit.</Description>
		<MaximumCharges>0</MaximumCharges>
	</PlayerAbility>

	<PlayerAbility>
		<AttributeName>Protection Fighting Style</AttributeName>
		<Description>When a creature you can see attacks a target other than you that is within 5 feet of you, you can use your reaction to impose disadvantage on the attack roll. You must be w ielding a shield.</Description>
		<MaximumCharges>0</MaximumCharges>
	</PlayerAbility>

	<PlayerAbility>
		<AttributeName>Two-Weapon Fighting Style</AttributeName>
		<Description>When you engage in two-weapon fighting, you can add your ability modifier to the damage of the second attack.</Description>
		<MaximumCharges>0</MaximumCharges>
	</PlayerAbility>
	
	<PlayerAbility>
		<AttributeName>Second Wind</AttributeName>
		<Description>You have a limited well of stamina that you can draw on to protect yourself from harm. On your turn, you can use a bonus action to regain hit points equal to 1d 10 + your fighter level. Once you use this feature, you must finish a short or long rest before you can use it again.</Description>
		<MaximumCharges>1</MaximumCharges>
	</PlayerAbility>
	
<!-- Barbarian class abilities -->
	
	<PlayerAbility>
		<AttributeName>Rage</AttributeName>
		<Description>In battle, you fight with primal ferocity. On your turn, you can enter a rage as a bonus action. While raging, you gain the following benefits if you aren’t wearing heavy armor:

• You have advantage on Strength checks and Strength saving throws.
• When you make a melee weapon attack using Strength, you gain a bonus to the damage roll that increases as you gain levels as a barbarian, as shown in the Rage Damage colum n of the Barbarian table. 
• You have resistance to bludgeoning, piercing, and slashing damage. If you are able to cast spells, you can’t cast them or concentrate on them while raging. 

Your rage lasts for 1 minute. It ends early if you are knocked unconscious or if your turn ends and you haven’t attacked a hostile creature since your last turn or taken damage since then. 
You can also end your rage on your turn as a bonus action. Once you have raged the number of times shown for your barbarian level in the Rages column of the Barbarian table, you must finish a long rest before you can rage again.</Description>
		<MaximumCharges>2</MaximumCharges>
		<IsToggle>true</IsToggle>
	</PlayerAbility>
		
	<PlayerAbility>
		<AttributeName>Unarmored Defense</AttributeName>
		<Description>While you are not wearing any armor, your Armor Class equals 10 + your Dexterity modifier + your Constitution modifier. You can use a shield and still gain this benefit.</Description>
		<MaximumCharges>0</MaximumCharges>
	</PlayerAbility>

<!-- Wizard class abilities -->
	<PlayerAbility>
		<AttributeName>Arcane Recovery</AttributeName>
		<Description>You have learned to regain some of your magical energy
by studying your spellbook. Once per day when you
finish a short rest, you can choose expended spell slots
to recover. The spell slots can have a combined level that
is equal to or less than half your wizard level (rounded
up), and none of the slots can be 6th level or higher.
For example, if you’re a 4th-level wizard, you can recover
up to two levels worth of spell slots. You can recover either
a 2nd-level spell slot or two 1st-level spell slots.</Description>
		<MaximumCharges>1</MaximumCharges>
	</PlayerAbility>
</ArrayOfPlayerAbility>
