<ArrayOfPlayerSpell xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Acid Splash</SpellName>
		<School>Conjuration</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>60</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
		
		<Description>You hurl a bubble of acid. Choose one creature within
range, or choose two creatures within range that are
within 5 feet of each other. A target must succeed on a
Dexterity saving throw or take 1d6 acid damage.
This spell’s damage increases by 1d6 when you reach
5th level (2d6), 11th level (3d6), and 17th level (4d6).</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Blade Ward</SpellName>
		<School>Abjuration</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
		
		<Description>You extend your hand and trace a sigil of warding in the
air. Until the end of your next turn, you have resistance
against bludgeoning, piercing, and slashing damage
dealt by weapon attacks.</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Chill Touch</SpellName>
		<School>Necromancy</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>120</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>1</SpellDuration>
		
		<Description>You create a ghostly, skeletal hand in the space of a
creature within range. Make a ranged spell attack
against the creature to assail it with the chill of the
grave. On a hit, the target takes 1d8 necrotic damage,
and it can’t regain hit points until the start of your next
turn. Until then, the hand clings to the target.
If you hit an undead target, it also has disadvantage on
attack rolls against you until the end of your next turn.
This spell’s damage increases by 1d8 when you reach
5th level (2d8), 11th level (3d8), and 17th level (4d8).</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Dancing Lights</SpellName>
		<School>Evocation</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>120</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
		
		<Description>You create up to four torch-sized lights within range,
making them appear as torches, lanterns, or glowing
orbs that hover in the air for the duration. You can
also combine the four lights into one glowing vaguely
humanoid form of Medium size. Whichever form you
choose, each light sheds dim light in a 10-foot radius.
As a bonus action on your turn, you can move the
lights up to 60 feet to a new spot within range. A light
must be within 20 feet of another light created by this
spell, and a light winks out if it exceeds the spell’s range.</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Fire Bolt</SpellName>
		<School>Evocation</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>120</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
		
		<Description>You hurl a mote of fire at a creature or object within
range. Make a ranged spell attack against the
target. On a hit, the target takes 1d10 fire damage. A
flammable object hit by this spell ignites if it isn't being
worn or carried. This spell’s damage increases by 1d10 when you reach
5th level (2d10), 11th level (3d10), and 17th level (4d10).</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Friends</SpellName>
		<School>Enchantment</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>false</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>true</IsConcentration>
		
		<Description>For the duration, you have advantage on all Charisma
checks directed at one creature o f your choice that isn’t
hostile toward you. When the spell ends, the creature
realizes that you used magic to influence its mood
and becomes hostile toward you. A creature prone
to violence might attack you. Another creature might
seek retribution in other ways (at the DM’s discretion),
depending on the nature o f your interaction with it.</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Light</SpellName>
		<School>Evocation</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>false</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>100</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
		
		<Description>You touch one object that is no larger than 10 feet in any
dimension. Until the spell ends, the object sheds bright
light in a 20-foot radius and dim light for an additional
20 feet. The light can be colored as you like. Completely
covering the object with something opaque blocks the
light. The spell ends if you cast it again or dismiss it
as an action. If you target an object held or worn by a hostile
creature, that creature must succeed on a Dexterity
saving throw to avoid the spell.</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Mage Hand</SpellName>
		<School>Conjuration</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_ACTION</CastingTime>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>30</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>false</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>10</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
		
		<Description>A spectral, floating hand appears at a point you choose
within range. The hand lasts for the duration or until
you dismiss it as an action. The hand vanishes if it is
ever more than 30 feet away from you or if you cast
this spell again. You can use your action to control the hand. You can
use the hand to manipulate an object, open an unlocked
door or container, stow or retrieve an item from an open
container, or pour the contents out o f a vial. You can
move the hand up to 30 feet each time you use it.
The hand can’t attack, activate magic items, or carry
more than 10 pounds.</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	<PlayerSpell>
		<SpellName>Mending</SpellName>
		<School>Transmutation</School>
		<CastingTime>CASTING_TIME_PERIOD</CastingTime>
		<CastingTimePeriod>10</CastingTimePeriod>
		<SpellLevel>0</SpellLevel>
		<SpellRange>0</SpellRange>
		<IsVerbalComponent>true</IsVerbalComponent>
		<IsSomaticComponent>true</IsSomaticComponent>
		<IsMaterialComponent>true</IsMaterialComponent>
		<SpellDuration>0</SpellDuration>
		<IsConcentration>false</IsConcentration>
		
		<Description>This spell repairs a single break or tear in an object
you touch, such as a broken chain link, two halves of
a broken key, a torn cloak, or a leaking wineskin. As
long as the break or tear is no larger than 1 foot in
any dimension, you mend it. leaving no trace of the
former damage. This spell can physically repair a magic item
or construct, but the spell can’t restore magic to
such an object.</Description>
	</PlayerSpell>
	
	
	
</ArrayOfPlayerSpell>