<ArrayOfCharacterBackGround xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
	<CharacterBackGround>
		<BackGroundName>Acolyte</BackGroundName>
		<Description>You have spent your life in the service of a temple to a specific god or pantheon of gods. You act as an intermediary between the realm of the holy and the mortal world, performing sacred rites and offering sacrifices in order to conduct worshipers into the presence of the divine. You are not necessarily a cleric - performing sacred rites is not the same thing as channeling divine power. </Description>
		<SkillProficiencies>
			<string>Insight</string>
			<string>Religion</string>
		</SkillProficiencies>
		<CustomLanguages>2</CustomLanguages>
		<Equipment>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>Holy Symbol</Name>
				<Quantity>1</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>Prayer Book</Name>
				<Quantity>1</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>Stick of Incence</Name>
				<Quantity>5</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>Vestments</Name>
				<Quantity>1</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>Common Clothes</Name>
				<Quantity>1</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
		</Equipment>
		<Gold>15</Gold>
		<Features>
			<BackGroundFeature>
				<Name>Shelter of the Faithful</Name>
				<Description>As an acolyte, you command the respect of those who share your faith, and you can perform the religious ceremonies of your deity. You and your adventuring companions can expect to receive free healing and care at a temple, shrine, or other established presence of your faith, though you must provide any material components needed for spells. Those who share your religion will support you (but only you) at a modest lifestyle. You might also have ties to a specific temple dedicated to your chosen deity or pantheon, and you have a residence there.  This could be the temple where you used to serve, if you remain on good terms with it, or a temple where you have found a new home. While near your temple, you can call upon the priests for assistance, provided the assistance you ask for is not hazardous and you remain in good standing with your temple.
				</Description>				
			</BackGroundFeature>
		</Features>
	</CharacterBackGround>
	
	<CharacterBackGround>
		<BackGroundName>Charlatan</BackGroundName>
		<Description>You have always had a way with people. You know what makes them tick, you can tease out their hearts' desires after a few minutes of conversation, and with a few leading questions you can read them like they were children's books. It’s a useful talent, and one that you’re perfectly willing to use for your advantage. You know what people want and you deliver, or rather, you promise to deliver. Common sense should steer people away from things that sound too good to be true, but common sense seems to be in short supply when you’re around. The bottle of pink-colored liquid will surely cure that unseemly rash, this ointment—nothing more than a bit of fat with a sprinkle of silver dust—can restore youth and vigor, and there’s a bridge in the city that just happens to be for sale. These marvels sound implausible, but you make them sound like the real deal.
		</Description>
		<SkillProficiencies>
			<string>Deception</string>
			<string>Sleight Of Hand</string>
		</SkillProficiencies>
		<ToolProficiencies>
			<string>Disguise Kit</string>
			<string>Forgery Kit</string>
		</ToolProficiencies>
		<Equipment>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>Fine Clothes</Name>
				<Quantity>1</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>Disguise Kit</Name>
				<Quantity>1</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>Tools of the Con of Your Choice</Name>
				<Quantity>1</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
		</Equipment>
		<Gold>15</Gold>
		<Features>
			<BackGroundFeature>
				<Name>False Identity</Name>
				<Description>You have created a second identity that includes documentation, established acquaintances, and disguises that allow you to assume that persona. Additionally, you can forge documents including official papers and personal letters, as long as you have seen an example of the kind of document or the handwriting you are trying to copy. \n
				</Description>				
			</BackGroundFeature>
		</Features>
	</CharacterBackGround>
	
	<CharacterBackGround>
		<BackGroundName>Criminal</BackGroundName>
		<Description>You are an experienced criminal with a history of breaking the law. You have spent a lot of time among other criminals and still have contacts within the criminal underworld. You’re far closer than most people to the world of murder, theft, and violence that pervades the underbelly of civilization, and you have survived up to this point by flouting the rules and regulations of society.</Description>
		<SkillProficiencies>
			<string>Deception</string>
			<string>Stealth</string>
		</SkillProficiencies>
		<ToolProficiencies>
			<string>Thieves' Tools</string>
			<string>AnyGaming</string>
		</ToolProficiencies>
		<Equipment>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>Crowbar</Name>
				<Quantity>1</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>Set of dark common clothes including a hood</Name>
				<Quantity>1</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
		</Equipment>
		<Gold>15</Gold>
		<Features>
			<BackGroundFeature>
				<Name>Criminal Contact</Name>
				<Description>You have a reliable and trustworthy contact who acts as your liaison to a network of other criminals. You know how to get messages to and from your contact, even over great distances; specifically, you know the local messengers, corrupt caravan masters, and seedy sailors who can deliver messages for you.</Description>				
			</BackGroundFeature>
		</Features>
	</CharacterBackGround>
	
	<CharacterBackGround>
		<BackGroundName>Entertainer</BackGroundName>
		<Description>You thrive in front of an audience. You know how to entrance them, entertain them, and even inspire them. Your poetics can stir the hearts of those who hear you, awakening grief or joy, laughter or anger. Your music raises their spirits or captures their sorrow. Your dance steps captivate, your humor cuts to the quick. Whatever techniques you use, your art is your life.</Description>
		<SkillProficiencies>
			<string>Acrobatics</string>
			<string>Performance</string>
		</SkillProficiencies>
		<ToolProficiencies>
			<string>Disguise Kit</string>
			<string>AnyMusical</string>
		</ToolProficiencies>
		<Equipment>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>AnyMusical</Name>
				<Quantity>1</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>the favor of an admirer (love letter, lock of hair, or trinket)</Name>
				<Quantity>1</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
		</Equipment>
		<Gold>15</Gold>
		<Features>
			<BackGroundFeature>
				<Name>By Popular Demand</Name>
				<Description>You can always find a place to perform, usually in an inn or tavern but possibly with a circus, at a theater, or even in a noble’s court. At such a place, you receive free lodging and food of a modest or comfortable standard (depending on the quality of the establishment), as long as you perform each night. In addition, your performance makes you something of a local figure. When strangers recognize you in a town where you have performed, they typically take a liking to you.</Description>				
			</BackGroundFeature>
		</Features>
	</CharacterBackGround>
	
	<CharacterBackGround>
		<BackGroundName>Folk Hero</BackGroundName>
		<Description>You come from a humble social rank, but you are destined for so much more. Already the people of your home village regard you as their champion, and your destiny calls you to stand against the tyrants and monsters that threaten the common folk everywhere.</Description>
		<SkillProficiencies>
			<string>Animal Handling</string>
			<string>Survival</string>
		</SkillProficiencies>
		<ToolProficiencies>
			<string>AnyArtisanProficiency</string>
			<string>Land Vehicles</string>
		</ToolProficiencies>
		<Equipment>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>AnyArtisans</Name>
				<Quantity>1</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>Shovel</Name>
				<Quantity>1</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>Iron Pot</Name>
				<Quantity>1</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>Common Clothes</Name>
				<Quantity>1</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
		</Equipment>
		<Gold>10</Gold>
		<Features>
			<BackGroundFeature>
				<Name>Rustic Hospitality</Name>
				<Description>Since you com e from the ranks of the common folk, you fit in among them with ease. You can find a place to hide, rest, or recuperate among other commoners, unless you have shown yourself to be a danger to them. They will shield you from the law or anyone else searching for you, though they will not risk their lives for you.</Description>				
			</BackGroundFeature>
		</Features>
	</CharacterBackGround>
	
	<CharacterBackGround>
		<BackGroundName>Guild Artisan</BackGroundName>
		<Description>You are a member of an artisan’s guild, skilled in a particular field and closely associated with other artisans. You are a well-established part of the mercantile world, freed by talent and wealth from the constraints of a feudal social order. You learned your skills as an apprentice to a master artisan, under the sponsorship of your guild, until you became a master in your own right.</Description>
		<SkillProficiencies>
			<string>Insight</string>
			<string>Persuasion</string>
		</SkillProficiencies>
		<ToolProficiencies>
			<string>AnyArtisanProficiency</string>
		</ToolProficiencies>
		<CustomLanguages>1</CustomLanguages>
		<Equipment>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>AnyArtisans</Name>
				<Quantity>1</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>Letter of introduction from your guild</Name>
				<Quantity>1</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
			<ContainerContent>
				<Name>Traveller's Clothes</Name>
				<Quantity>1</Quantity>
			</ContainerContent>
		</Equipment>
		<Gold>15</Gold>
		<Features>
			<BackGroundFeature>
				<Name>Guild Membership</Name>
				<Description>As an established and respected member of a guild, you can rely on certain benefits that membership provides. Your fellow guild members will provide you with lodging and food if necessary, and pay for your funeral if needed. In some cities and towns, a guildhall offers a central place to meet other members of your profession, which can be a good place to meet potential patrons, allies, or hirelings. Guilds often wield tremendous political power. If you are accused of a crime, your guild will support you if a good case can be made for your innocence or the crime is justifiable. You can also gain access to powerful political figures through the guild, if you are a member in good standing. Such connections might require the donation of money or magic items to the guild’s coffers. You must pay dues of 5 gp per month to the guild. If you miss payments, you must make up back dues to remain in the guild’s good graces.</Description>				
			</BackGroundFeature>
		</Features>
	</CharacterBackGround>
	
	
</ArrayOfCharacterBackGround>